<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="27"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[No. of students  who are not  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  No. of students selected for Higher  Studies  No. of students selected for Higher  Studies



                         2014-15                        584  1455  366                  148    171  230

                                            No. of students  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  from the Private  Bodies



                             -  -   -                   0    0    0              Median salary of  placed graduates(Amount in  Rs.)  122500(One Lakh Twenty Two Thousand  130000(One Lakh  Thirty Thousand)  180000(One Lakh  Eighty Thousand)  Median salary of  placed graduates(Amount in  Rs.)

                                            No. of students  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  from Institution  Funds  Five Hundred )


                         2015-16                        4    46   1


                                            No. of students  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  from the State  and Central  Government  No. of students  placed  No. of students  placed


                             -  -   -                   12   186  39                    28     39  24




                         2016-17            Socially  Challenged  (SC+ST+OBC  Including male  & female)  210  673  170  No. of students  graduating in minimum stipulated  time  No. of students  graduating in minimum stipulated  time
      National Institutional Ranking Framework


                                            Economically  Backward  (Including male  & female)  390  1014  236  Academic Year  Academic Year
                                1055                                                    217    286  352
                             -      -

        Ministry of Education Government of India Welcome to Data Capturing System: OVERALL  2017-18  Outside  Country  (Including male  & female)  32  2017-18  2018-19  2019-20









                                            Outside State  (Including male  & female)  32  42  26  0  0  0
                             360  1240  -               0         0              No. of students  admitted through  Lateral entry  No. of students  admitted through  Lateral entry





                         2018-19            Within State  (Including male  & female)  Academic Year          Academic Year
                 Institute Name: Charotar University of Science & Technology [IR-O-U-0128]




                             540  1400  728             1293  4781  1007                2016-17  2017-18  2018-19
                                            Total Students  1325  4855  1033     No. of first year students admitted in  the year  No. of first year students admitted in  the year




                         2019-20         Total Actual Student Strength (Program(s) Offered by Your Institution)  No. of Female  Students  621  1451  578  UG [3 Years Program(s)]: Placement & higher studies for previous 3 years  245  317  384 UG [4 Years Program(s)]: Placement & higher studies for previous 3 years

               Submitted Institute Data for NIRF'2021'  Sanctioned (Approved) Intake  Academic Year  570 UG [3 Years Program(s)]  1400 UG [4 Years Program(s)]  684 PG [2 Year Program(s)]  No. of Male (All programs  Students of all years)  704 UG [3 Years  Program(s)]  3404 UG [4 Years  Program(s)]  455 PG [2 Year  Program(s)]  Placement & Higher Studies  No. of first year Academic Year students intake in the  year  240 2015-16  300 2016-17  360 2017-18  No. of first year]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[No. of students selected for Higher  Studies




     293  342  258               28  25     46



     230000(Two Lakh  Thirty Thousand)  240000(Two Lakh  Forty Thousand)  310000(Three Lakh  Ten Thousand )  Median salary of  placed graduates(Amount in  Rs.)  220000(Two Lakh  Twenty Thousand)  225000(Two Lakh  Twenty Five  Thousand)  240000(Two Lakh  Forty Thousand)  2017-18  2017-18  Utilised Amount  19205211 (One Crore Ninety Two Lakh Five Thousand Two 41865577 (Four Crore Eighteen Lakh Sixty Five Thousand Five Hundred Seventy Seven) 815500 (Eight Lakh Fifteen Thousa








                         No. of students  placed         Total Students   13  20                  Hundred Eleven)




     555  589  468               404  354   274


                         No. of students graduating in minimum  stipulated time                   Thousand Nine Hundred Four)




     932  1048  956                                                    2018-19        2018-19  Utilised Amount  15797904 (One Crore Fifty Seven Lakh Ninety Seven 21883712 (Two Crore Eighteen Lakh Eighty Three Thousand 1277315 (Twelve Lakh Seventy Seven Thousand Three 24261936 (Two Crore Forty Two Lakh Sixty One Thousand







     2017-18  2018-19  2019-20   594  579   556       Ph.D (Student pursuing doctoral program till 2019-20 Students admitted in the academic year 2020-21 should not be entered here.)  78  142 No. of Ph.D students graduated (including Integrated Ph.D)  5  23  Annual Capital Expenditure on Academic Activities and Resources (excluding expenditure on buildings)  Seven Hundred Twelve)  Hundred Fifteen)  Nine Hundred Thirty Six)









                         Academic Year                                 2019-20        2019-20  Utilised Amount  14531669 (One Crore Forty Five Lakh Thirty One Thousand  1844692 (Eighteen Lakh Forty Four Thousand Six Hundred 76140825 (Seven Crore Sixty One Lakh Forty Thousand Eight
     184  157  143






                      PG [2 Years Program(s)]: Placement & higher studies for previous 3 years
     2015-16  2016-17  2017-18   2017-18  2018-19  2019-20                                        Six Hundred Sixty Nine) 12893238 (One Crore Twenty Eight Lakh Ninety Three Thousand Two Hundred Thirty Eight)  Hundred Twenty Five)



                         No. of first year students admitted in  the year  7  28                           Ninety Two)





     862  959  923               648  666   570                                    Financial Resources: Utilised Amount for the Capital expenditure for previous 3 years


                         No. of first year students intake in the  year




     955  955  1055              777  794   728                                       Academic Year            Other expenditure on creation of Capital Assets (excluding


                         Academic Year             Ph.D Student Details                              New Equipment for Laboratories  Engineering Workshops  expenditure on Land and Building)


     2014-15  2015-16  2016-17   2016-17  2017-18  2018-19  Full Time  Part Time  Full Time  Part Time  Library]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[2017-18  Utilised Amount 349101375 (Thirty Four Crore Ninety One Lakh One Thousand 255854100 (Twenty Five Crore Fifty Eight Lakh Fifty Four  3001167 (Thirty Lakh One Thousand One Hundred Sixty  2017  2017-18  One Crore Seventy Four Lakh Fifty Nine Thousand Two  2017-18  Thirty Two Lakh Twenty Six Thousand Five Hundred One  2017-18

                      Three Hundred Seventy Five)  Thousand One Hundred)  Seven)  0  1  24  13  17459226  Hundred Twenty Six  21  15  3226501  1  22





















           2018-19  Utilised Amount  380929793 (Thirty Eight Crore Nine Lakh Twenty Nine Thousand Seven Hundred Ninety Three) 257064165 (Twenty Five Crore Seventy Lakh Sixty Four Thousand One Hundred Sixty Five) 5663720 (Fifty Six Lakh Sixty Three Thousand Seven Hundred  2018  2018-19  Eighty Five Lakh Five Thousand Three Hundred Thirty Four  2018-19  Sixty Five Lakh One Thousand Nine Hundred Twenty Nine  2018-19






                 Annual Operational Expenditure  Twenty)  2  1  21  9  8505334      46  22  6501929         1    28













        Financial Resources: Utilised Amount for the Operational expenditure for previous 3 years

           2019-20  Utilised Amount 406457152 (Forty Crore Sixty Four Lakh Fifty Seven Thousand 291589402 (Twenty Nine Crore Fifteen Lakh Eighty Nine 4839047 (Forty Eight Lakh Thirty Nine Thousand Forty Seven)  2019  2019-20  Seventy One Lakh Eighty Five Thousand Seven Hundred Sixty  2019-20  Eighty Five Lakh Twenty Eight Thousand Five Hundred Sixty  2019-20


                      One Hundred Fifty Two)  Thousand Four Hundred Two)  0  1  18  8  7185768  Eight  37  34  8528563  Three  1  28

















                     Salaries (Teaching and Non Teaching staff)  Seminars/Conferences/Workshops  IPR  No. of Patents Published  No. of Patents Granted  Sponsored Research Details  Total no. of Sponsored Projects  Total no. of Funding Agencies Total Amount Received (Amount in Rupees)  Amount Received in Words  Consultancy Project Details  Total no. of Consultancy Projects  Total no. of Client Organizations Total Amount Received (Amount in Rupees)  Amount Received in Words
           Academic Year  Maintenance of Academic Infrastructure or consumables and other running expenditures(excluding maintenance of hostels and allied services,rent of the building, depreciation cost, etc)  Calendar year  Financial Year  Financial Year  Executive Development Program/Management Development Programs  Financial Year Total no. of Executive Development Programs/ Management]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Association type  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular







                                                                 Leaving Date  --  --  --  --  --  --   --    --


          Nine Lakh Ninety Thousand                  CGPA        Joining Date






     990000                                                            19-07-2014  01-04-2016  01-04-2016  16-08-2018  01-09-2018  01-09-2018  18-06-2019  05-06-2017




                                                                 Currently  working with  institution?


                                                        3.11           Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes



          Fourteen Lakh Eighty Four Thousand  Yes, more than 80% of the buildings  Yes, more than 80% of the buildings  Is Associated  Last Year  Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes









     1484000          Yes                NO      YES             Experience (In  Months)  84  107  63  130  148  206  17  47
                                                     Valid upto


                                                                 Qualification  Ph.D  MCA  MCA  MCA  Ph.D  Ph.D  MCA  M. Phil











          Twelve Lakh Sixty Thousand                    24-05-2021  Gender  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male





     1260000          2. Do your institution have provision for walking aids, includingwheelchairs and transportation from one building to another for 3. Do your institution buildings have specially designed toilets for handicapped students?  Valid from  Designation  Age  Assistant  28  Professor  Assistant  31  Professor  Assistant  29  Professor  Assistant  38  Professor  Assistant  37  Professor  Assistant  40  Professor  Assistant  23  Professor  Other  28




















       & Boarding Charges) Total Annual Earnings (Amount in Rupees)(Excluding Lodging  Total Annual Earnings in Words PCS Facilities: Facilities of physically challenged students 1. Do your institution buildings have Lifts/Ramps?  handicapped students?  Accreditation  NBA Accreditation 1.Does your institute have a valid NBA Accreditation?  NAAC Accreditation 1. Does your institute have a valid NAAC Accreditation?  25-05-2016  Faculty Details  Name  Srno  SANNI DILIPBHAI]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular









     --     --    --   --    --   --    --  --  --   --    --    --   --    --   --    --   --    --    --   --



     21-08-2004  18-07-2011  01-02-2016  08-08-2013  09-03-2009  18-01-2016  14-03-2009  19-10-2016  30-10-2006  01-02-2016  01-04-2001  11-07-2002  22-06-2006  13-03-2007  17-05-2013  01-04-2017  16-01-2012  08-06-2010  01-04-2016  05-07-2017









     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  No






     200    135   144  118   140  66    242  43  166  88   229   217  180   161  104   112  145   151   71   120







     Ph.D   MCA   M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  B.Sc.  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.E.






     Male   Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male





     Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     40     34    36   35    40   28    42  28  37   30    42    39   36    35   32    42   36    36    30   31

     MAYURKUMAR  PRAVINCHANDR  A SUTARIA  ABHILASH  MAHESHKUMAR  SHUKLA  ABHISHEK  SWARNKAR  ABHISHEK  NATHALAL  DADHANIA  ADITI D BUCH  AKASH  VISHNUPRASAD  VYAS  ALPANA N PATEL  ALPESHSINH  DUDABHAI VALA  AMIT AMBALAL  PATEL  AMIT  MANSUKHLAL  PARMAR  AMIT  PRAVINCHANDR  A GANATRA  AMIT RAMANLAL  THAKKAR  AMITKUMAR  JAYDEVBHAI  NAYAK  AMITKUMAR  VINUBHAI PATEL  AMRINBANU  MOHAMMADHAN  IF SHAIKH  ANAMIKA  SANJAY JHA  ANAND  PURSHOTAMBH  AI PATEL  ANIL SURESH  CHAND SHARM












     9      10    11   12    13   14    15  16  17   18    19    20   21    22   23    24   25    26    27   28]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





            29-06-2019  21-01-2020               30-09-2019


     --              --    --     --  --   --           --    --    --    --   --    --    --     --    --    --



     25-08-2011  18-07-2016  01-09-2017  04-08-2016  19-06-2014  18-11-2010  01-02-2016  01-12-2016  06-09-2010  01-10-2015  23-07-2002  13-03-2007  04-09-2017  09-07-2010  03-07-2017  17-12-2008  01-07-2015  06-05-2005  11-04-2011









     Yes    No    No  Yes  Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  No     Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes






     122    36    76  65   99     502  120  107  123    97    217   161   62   327   455   192    474   242   133



                  M.Sc.(Nursing)     M.Sc.(Nursing)


     Ph.D   BPT      M.E.  M.Tech  Ph.D    Ph.D  MBA    MCA   M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  B.Sc.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D





     Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female






     Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant  Professor










     34     28    31  29   32     73  34   35    34     30    41    37    30   57    65    39     62    51    34




     ANJALI  PUSHKAR  TIWARI  ANJALIBEN  MAHESHBHAI  PATEL  ANJU  JACKSON  ANKIT  JAYESHKUMAR  WANKAWALA  ANKUR  HARSADBHAI  PATEL  ARABINDA  RAY  ARPAN  JAYPRAKASH  PANDYA  ARPAN  HARISHKUMAR  DESAI  ARPIT  RAJESHBHAI  PATEL  ARPIT  RASESHKUMAR  TRIVEDI  ARPITA  JIGNESHKUMAR  SHAH  ARPITA  PINALKUMAR  PATEL  ARTEE  TYAGI  ARUNA  PRABHASHANKA  R JANI  ARVINDBHAI  BHULABHAI  PATEL  ASHWINKUMAR  BHANUPRASAD  MAKWANA  ASHWINKUMAR  DHULABHAI  PATEL  ATUL MANUBHAI  PATEL  AVAN









     29     30    31  32   33     34  35   36    37     38    39    40    41   42    43    44     45    46    47]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                                                                                          10-10-2019      30-04-2020


     --     --     --   --   --    --   --  --   --     --    --    --    --   --    --        --    --         --



     17-01-2011  29-04-2009  09-06-2016  03-10-2012  16-04-2004  07-07-2014  09-01-2009  19-01-2013  16-01-2017  11-08-2005  02-05-2016  01-02-2016  01-02-2008  01-01-2013  27-04-2004  28-06-2014  02-08-2010  01-04-2016  01-06-2011  20-07-2015









     Yes    Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  No   Yes   Yes  No    Yes







     Yes    Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes






     115    167    74   442  216   88   456  121  129   177   132   106   184  122   196  125  121   77   181   65






     M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  MBBS  M.E.  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Sc.(Nursing)  MBA  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  Ph.D







     Male   Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male





     Assistant  Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     32     39     37   69   40    41   63  32   35     37    38    33    49   33    40   33   32    29   38    40

       VIJAYKUMAR  BALAGANAPATH  MURUGANANTH  KHODNAPUR  BHARAT G  BHASKAR  KANAIYALAL  BHASKARJYOTI  BHAVIK SHELAT  HARESHKUMAR  BHAVTOSH  ANILKUMAR  HARIVADAN  DHARMINKUMAR  BINITKUMAR  NAINESHBHAI  BRAGADISH D  LAXMANBHAI  KUNDALIYA  BRIJESH N SHAH  HARDIK SHAH  MAHESHKUMAR  CHIRAG  JAIN  INDRAVADANBH  RAMESHCHAND  RA DESAI


     AXAT  PATEL  Y  AN M  BAPU  PATEL  PANDYA  BORAH  BHAVIN  MEHTA  KIKANI  BIMAL  PATEL  BINAL  JOSHI  PATEL  IYER  BRIJESH  CHANDNI  CHINTAN  BHATT  CHIRAG  AI PATEL  CHIRAYU








     48     49     50   51   52    53   54  55   56     57    58    59    60   61    62   63   64    65   66    67]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                                                                                                           08-02-2020


     --     --    --   --    --    --  --  --   --   --    --      --    --    --   --    --    --    --         --



     10-10-2011  24-07-2007  05-06-2017  25-08-2011  01-06-2015  11-01-2000  23-06-2014  12-08-2017  13-10-2008  16-08-2004  01-09-2010  23-06-2014  01-10-2015  05-08-2003  01-06-2009  04-10-2017  02-08-2010  16-02-2009  17-05-2013  03-07-2017









     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  No    Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes






     188    265   85   128   79    291  108  56  176  199  138     89    129   204  148   47    120   138  93    44



                       M.Sc.(Nursing)


     Ph.D   Ph.D  M.Sc.      M.E.  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  MCA  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech






     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female


     Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor













     44     44    30   35    31    50  31  35   35   42    35      29    36    37   39    31    32    35   30    27
     DARSHANKUMA  R HASMUKHBHAI  PATEL  DATTATRAYA  GANPATRAO  SUBHEDAR  DEBAYAN DILIP  BAIDYA  DEEPAK  KRISHNAMURTH  Y  DEVANG  GHANSHYAMBH  AI PATEL  DEVANG JOSHI  DHARA MILAN  PATEL  DHARA NRUPAL  PATEL  DHARA PINKESH  PATEL  DHARMENDRA  TRIKAMLAL  PATEL  DHARMENDRASI  NH  VIRENDRASINH  CHAUHAN  DHARMESHSINH  AJMALSINH  DABHI  DHATRI  KIRANBHAI  RAVAL  DHAVALKUMAR  AMBALAL BHOI  DHRUVKUMAR  PARESHKUMAR  DAVE  DIJITKUMAR  MAHENDRABHAI  PATEL  DIPALI  YOGESHBHAI  PATEL













     68     69    70   71    72    73  74  75   76   77    78      79    80    81   82    83    84    85   86    87]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                                                                                        08-02-2020      31-10-2019


     --   --    --   --   --   --   --  --   --   --    --   --   --    --   --    --         --    --     --    --



     01-04-2016  01-02-2016  24-04-2007  08-01-2009  29-04-2009  03-05-2007  18-07-2019  07-02-2008  02-12-2013  01-07-2015  09-01-2017  15-09-2007  29-03-2012  01-12-2016  06-05-2006  09-06-2009  17-05-2013  01-01-2009  04-11-2015  15-06-2011  01-06-2015  01-02-2016









     Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  No    Yes   Yes  No  Yes  Yes







     Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes







     66   61    194  139  146  175  36  250  113  107   72   167  183   49   256   157  103   144   525  435  113  63


     M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.E.









     Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male






     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Lecturer  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     30   29    42   41   37   38   27  46   34   32    29   37   38    31   44    36   32    33    69  66  32   30


     DIVYA  JAIN  PACHORI  DIVYESH  BHUPENDRABHA  I  PATEL  ANJANA  KOTHARI  C K SUMESH  MANSI K SONI  FALGUNI  AMBALAL RAVAL  FRANNY JOEL  EMMANUEL  GAJANAN S  PATANGE  GARGI KETUL  RAY  GAURANG  ARVINDBHAI  PATEL  GAURAV VILAS  KAPSE  GAYATRI A DAVE  GAYATRIBAHEN  CHHAGANBHAI  PATEL  GLORY JAYESH  WAGHELA  GOVIND  BHASKARBHAI  DAVE  HARDIK P MODI  HARDIK  RAMESHCHAND  RA MANDORA  HARDIK  SUDHIRBHAI  JAYSWAL  HARESH JANI  HARISH DESAI  HARMISH  GOPALBHAI  BHATT  HARSH  P











     88   89    90   91   92   93   94  95   96   97    98   99   100   101  102   103  104   105   106  107  108  109]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                  06-02-2020                   31-01-2020


     --     --          --    --    --     --       --    --     --    --    --    --   --    --    --     --  --



     01-04-2016  01-01-2009  01-07-2014  01-08-2017  12-10-2015  01-04-2016  22-06-2009  23-07-2002  13-10-2008  01-01-2003  01-07-2014  27-12-2011  15-11-2010  25-09-2017  20-08-2007  11-09-2017  16-07-2012  01-04-2016  17-09-2007









     Yes    Yes   No    Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  No  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes







     57     157   70    35    105   146    131  214  142  211    121   104   180   115  156   45    113    82  152



     MPT(Physio)  M.E.  M.Tech  MPT(Physio)  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D









     Male   Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female





     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     31     35    31    28    32    39     35  38   33    41     31    32    40    35   36    27    33     31  40
       MAHENDRAKUM  NANDLALBHAI  HASMUKHBHAI  JITENDRABHAI  HIMANSHU A  HIREN KANTILAL  NATVARLAL  KAMLESHBHAI  PUSHAKARBHAI  NAVINCHANDRA  JALPA HARSHIT  VASHISHTHKUM  AR SUTHAR  ASHOKBHAI  HARKISHANBHAI


     HEMAL  AR PATEL  HEMANT  YADAV  HENISH  SHAH  HETA  RAJNIKANT  PATEL  HETAL  SHAH  HETALBEN  PUNJABHAI  PATEL  PATEL  MEWADA  HITESH  PATEL  HITESHRI  SHASTRI  JAGRAT  MEHTA  JAGRUTI  BRIJESH  PRAJAPATI  JAIMIN  UNDAVIA  DESAI  JALPA  JALPABEN  PRAJAPATI  JALPESH  VASA  JAMIN  CHAUHAN  JANKI N  THAKKER








     110    111   112   113   114   115    116  117  118  119    120   121   122   123  124   125   126    127  128]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





          01-07-2019                                                        21-10-2019


     --         --     --    --   --  --     --  --     --  --     --    --       --   --    --   --    --     --



     01-06-2011  01-06-2017  11-01-2016  16-01-2017  18-01-2016  30-06-2014  16-01-2012  01-01-2009  18-01-2016  04-07-2017  21-03-2007  01-06-2012  09-01-2009  23-06-2014  09-07-2007  01-02-2008  18-01-2016  01-01-2014  01-08-2001  23-06-2011









     Yes  No    Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  No  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes







     Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes






     133  59    59     105   143  74  103    139  61    110  217   142   216  104  157  150  73   274   233    158






     M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  Master of  Optometry  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D







     Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male





     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     38   29    28     29    35   31  32     33  28     33  48     36    45  31   36   36    28   49    44     40
     JAY KIRITKUMAR  BHAVSAR  JAY  RAMESHBHAI  PATEL  JAYDEEP  NILESHBHAI  DESAI  JAYDEVSINH  DHANRAJ  PARGARA  JAYESH  PATIDAR  JESAL ANVESH  DESAI  JIGAR  SUBODHCHAND  RA SARDA  JIGNESH J  PATOLIYA  JIGNESHKUMAR  SUBHASBHAI  PATEL  JIMITKUMAR  RATILAL PATEL  JITENDRA  PRABHAKAR  CHAUDHARI  JIVANADHAR  ASHOKKUMAR  JOSHI  KALAPI PATEL  KAMLESH  RAMJIBHAI  MAKVANA  KAMLESH V  CHAUHAN  KANANKUMARI  GAMANLAL  GAMIT  KANCHAL  DAVE  KANUBHAI  KHODIDAS  PATEL  KARTIKBHAI  SHASH












     129  130   131    132   133  134  135   136  137   138  139   140   141  142  143  144  145  146   147    148]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                              23-12-2019                    21-03-2020


     --     --    --    --          --   --    --     --          --    --    --     --    --    --   --   --     --



     13-06-2011  20-06-2011  01-02-2016  13-10-2008  04-04-2016  02-06-2011  16-01-2017  01-08-2011  01-02-2016  01-04-2016  22-07-2013  01-04-2016  01-06-2015  23-07-2011  01-09-2017  15-09-2015  25-01-2016  01-06-2012  10-05-2007









     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   No    Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   No    Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes






     129    122   68    154   84    132  57    131    75    60    104   52    106    109   69    175  85   105    159






     M. Phil  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M. Phil  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  M.E.  M.E.  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male





     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor










     35     33    29    35    29    46   32    35     33    29    33    28    32     32    30    38   32   33     41



     KAUSHIK  ROHITKUMAR  TRIVEDI  KEYUR  KAMALDASJI  MAHANT  KHUSHBOO  HIRENKUMAR  KAVAR  KILLOL  VISHNUPRASAD  PANDYA  KINJAL  PREMPRAKASH  BHATIA  KINNARI  PAREKH  KIRANKUMAR  GORDHANBHAI  PATEL  KIRTI  JAYANTIBHAI  MAKWANA  KISHAN  PIYUSHBHAI  PATEL  KRISHNA  KIRANKUMAR  BHATT  KRUNALKUMAR  BHUPENDRABHA  I KACHHIIA  KRUPABEN  DHIRENDRAKUM  AR SHAH  KRUTI  JAYESHBHAI  DHYANI  KUNDAN  MOHANBHAI  PATEL  LIPI  TEJENDRABHAI  ACHARYA  LOUREMBAM  SURBALA DEVI  MADHAV  NITINB









     149    150   151   152   153   154  155   156    157   158   159   160   161    162   163   164  165  166    167]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





     03-10-2017  --  --  --   --   --    --    --   --   --    --    --   --    --     --    --    --   --   --  --







     20-01-2014  18-04-2011  21-12-2007  27-06-2011  01-09-2009  17-05-2013  29-06-2017  02-02-2015  01-04-2016  06-03-2009  26-06-2015  12-12-2007  18-01-2016  18-01-2016  01-09-2015  23-06-2014  01-08-2007  21-07-2012  07-07-2017  09-07-2012










     No     Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes






     No     Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes






     104    109   157   122   141  108   79    115  60   153   62    152  83    84     60    98    156  97   92  97







     Ph.D   Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M. Pharm  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech






     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male





     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     33     32    38    33    33   32    34    35   29   36    27    36   31    29     31    32    37   32   31  31

     MANANKUMAR  NARESHKUMAR  SHAH  MANTHAN  SUDHIRBHAI  MANAVADARIA  MARTIN  KANTILAL  PARMAR  MAULIK  JASHVANTLAL  SHAH  MAULIK V SHAH  MAYURI  JAMANADAS  POPAT  MEERA  HARDEVSINH  CHUDASAMA  MEGHA JEMIN  DESAI  MEGHA NISHITH  GOHIL  MEHUL  MANUBHAI  PATEL  MEHULKUMAR  PRAVINBHAI  KATAKIYA  MIHIR A BHATT  MIHIR  SIDDHARTH  MEHTA  MIHIRKUMAR  RAMESHBHAI  PATEL  MILAPKUMAR  RAJESHBHAI  PATEL  MIRAL  MUKESHBHAI  DESAI  MITALI U  VEDANTI  MOCHI PRATIK  KANTILAL  MOHAMMAD  H











     168    169   170   171   172  173   174   175  176  177   178   179  180   181    182   183   184  185  186  187]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular









     --     --  --   --   --   --    --    --    --     --    --    --    --    --   --    --     --    --    --



     10-07-2006  02-01-2017  01-04-2016  01-09-2017  01-04-2010  01-07-2010  23-06-2014  01-01-2019  13-07-2006  01-04-2016  27-12-2007  18-07-2011  02-07-2007  09-06-2015  18-01-2016  01-07-2008  18-08-2005  07-07-2008  05-07-2018









     Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes







     Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes






     169    176  133  35  121  128   85    82    169    72    152   110   308   70   59    145    181   157   39







     M.E.   Ph.D  MCA  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  MPT(Physio)  M.Tech  MCA  Ph.D  MCA  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech






     Male   Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male





     Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     37     38  34   41   47   35    29    31    35     28    36    33    47    30   28    35     39    37    29
     MRUGENDRASIN  H LAXMANSINH  RAHEVAR  MRUNALI  RASHMIN PATEL  MUBINA SHAQIL  MALIK  MURALI MOHAN  SHARAFF  NEERAJ  DEVENDRA JAIN  NEHA  HIRENSINH  RAJPUT  NEHAL  SANDIPKUMAR  PATEL  NENCY  KALPESHBHAI  PANDYA  NIKITA  MAHESHKUMAR  BHATT  NILAM  SANATKUMAR  DESAI  NILAY  DHIRENKUMAR  SOLANKI  NILAY  PRAVINCHANDR  A GANATRA  NILAYKUMAR  ARVINDBHAI  PATEL  NILESH KUMAR  DUBEY  NIPUN  DILIPKUMAR  GOSAI  NIRAJ  YASHVANTRAI  VYAS  NIRALI  NIKHILKUMAR  HONEST  NIRAV  HASMUKH












     188    189  190  191  192  193  194   195   196    197   198   199   200   201  202   203    204   205   206]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular









     --     --  --     --  --     --    --     --   --    --     --  --     --  --     --    --    --    --   --



     23-07-2013  10-09-2015  02-01-2017  21-12-2015  01-05-2004  01-02-2016  05-07-2018  01-09-2012  05-07-2018  01-06-2012  27-08-2012  05-07-2011  01-11-2000  01-01-2007  19-07-2010  25-02-2011  23-06-2014  17-05-2013  04-02-2014









     Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes







     Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes






     169    168  131   116  195   66    25     125  28    98     94  158    386  169   130   130   85    135  109






     M. Phil  MPT(Physio)  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.






     Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male






     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     40     40  32     48  40     29    27     43   28    32     36  39     60  38     35    32    29    36   31



     NIRUBEN  CHETANBHAI  PATEL  P RATAN  KHUMAN  PADMAVATHI  JAGDISHPRASA  D BINDULAL  PALASH  MANDAL  PARTH  DILIPKUMAR  SHAH  PATEL  SANDIPKUMAR  PANKAJBHAI  PATHARIYA  SARASWATI  CHANDRAPALSI  NGH  PINAL CHIRAG  PATEL  PINKIBEN  MAHAVIRPRASA  D SHARMA  POONAM  JAYANTIBHAI  THANKI  PRABHIN  SUKUMARAN  PRAKASH  VAIDHIYALINGA  M  PRAKASH  JOHNBHAI DABHI  PRANAV  DHIMANTKUMAR  DESAI  PRANAV  JYOTISHBHAI  VYAS  PRATIK  BHANUBHAI  PANCHAL  PRITESHKUMAR  NATAVARLAL  PRAJAPAT









     207    208  209   210  211   212   213    214  215   216    217  218   219  220   221   222   223   224  225]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                     27-11-2019               25-06-2019


     --     --  --         --     --    --          --    --     --    --    --    --    --     --    --    --   --



     08-06-2006  01-09-2008  02-07-2012  18-01-2016  04-10-2019  17-07-2014  24-03-2011  16-08-2017  15-07-2011  23-07-2013  01-07-2015  03-11-2011  06-08-2012  25-07-2012  10-07-2017  17-05-2013  29-10-2007  03-09-2010  12-09-2008









     Yes    Yes  Yes  No   Yes    Yes   Yes   No    Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes







     Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes






     179    390  106  66   48     73    203   14    124   121    69    514   120   121   181    103   167   151  143






     M.Tech  Ph.D  MCA  M.Tech  M. Phil  M.Tech  MBA  M. Phil  MBA  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M. Phil






     Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female






     Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     37     60  32   28    29     29    40    28    34    34     35    73    35    35    41     33    37    40   35
       HARISHKUMAR  PRAJAPATI  R V UPADHYAY  SUNILKUMAR  RAHULKUMAR  BHARATKUMAR  RAJANIKANT  GIRJASHANKAR  RAJENDRA  RAJENDRAKUMA  R BABUBHAI  KANAYALAL  SADHWANI  VASANTBHAI  RAJESHKUMAR  VISHNUBHAI  RAJNIKANT  RAMESHWARI  MEGHNADSINH  RANDHAWA  KAWALJITSINGH  MANSINGH  BHARATBHAI  RAVIKUMAR  JANAKBHAI  RESHMA GUNAJI  RESHMABEN  ROHITKUMAR


     PURVI     RACHANA  PATEL  SONI  BABUBHAI  VANKAR  RAJAT  PANDEY  VINUBHAI  SOLANKI  CHAUHAN  RAJESH  RAJESH  SAVALIA  PATEL  MULJIBHAI  PATEL  ZALA  RASHMIN  PATEL  VIJAYBHAI  PATEL  RAVISH  PATEL  SABLE  SANJHIRA








     226    227  228  229  230    231   232   233   234   235    236   237   238   239   240    241   242   243  244]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                                                      23-08-2019


     --     --    --    --    --    --     --  --         --     --  --     --    --    --    --    --     --  --



     01-02-2016  27-12-2012  01-05-2004  29-10-2013  01-06-2013  15-07-2010  01-09-2017  01-02-2016  01-04-2016  01-02-2016  13-10-2008  19-01-2011  16-08-2016  04-08-2008  01-07-2016  17-08-2017  01-06-2013  12-08-2010  08-08-2013









     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   No  Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes







     51     118   195   166   86    149    57  82     95  93     161  115   50    144   186   154   92     175  92






     Ph.D   M.Tech  Ph.D  M. Phil  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  MCA  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D






     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female





     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     28     34    38    38    31    42     41  31     31  31     37  32     28    40    39    41    31     38  34


     RIKIKUMAR  HASMUKHBHAI  PATEL  RIKIN  JAYDEVBHAI  NAYAK  RITESH  PRAVINBHAI  PATEL  ROBERT  JOSEPH  PARMAR  RONAKKUMAR  NATAVARLAL  PATEL  RUCHA  PRADIPKUMAR  DESAI  RUCHI  CHATURVEDI  RUGNESHKUMA  R RAMESHBHAI  PATEL  RUPAL SAVAN  PATEL  SAGAR  MUKESHBHAI  PATEL  SAGAR B PATEL  SAGAR  RAMCHANDRA  CHOKSHI  SAGARKUMAR  JAGDISHBHAI  PATEL  SAMIR  GUNVANTBHAI  PATEL  SANDIP  BHIKHUBHAI  PATEL  SANJAYKUMAR  HEMRAJ  PANJABI  SANKETKUMAR  BHARATBHAI  SUTHAR  SANSKRUTI  VRI










     245    246   247   248   249   250    251  252   253  254   255  256   257   258   259   260   261    262  263]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





     21-11-2019  --  --  --  07-12-2019  05-03-2020  07-08-2019  --  --  --  24-07-2019  --  30-04-2020  --  --  --  --  --  --







     13-12-2004  01-01-2014  01-10-2008  04-02-2010  01-04-2016  01-01-2016  01-04-2016  01-07-2016  10-08-2017  01-02-2016  20-06-2014  01-01-2014  21-07-2011  28-03-2016  01-01-2014  01-07-2010  01-10-2015  14-04-2011  01-09-2010










     No   Yes   Yes  Yes  No    No   No    Yes  Yes   Yes   No     Yes   No    Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes






     Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes






     220  96    215  252  105   334  56    132  45    138   121    84    110   52    93    152    156   153   119







     Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  B.Sc.  MCA  DOMS  MPT(Physio)  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  MBA  M.E.  M.Tech  MCA  MPT(Physio)  M.E.  Ph.D  MCA  Ph.D  Ph.D






     Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male





     Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     47   36    55   42   33    50   29    36   27    37    31     30    31    28    31    37     38    36    32
     SARMAN KHIMA  HADIA  SATAYU  CHANDRASHEKH  AR TRAVADI  SEEMA R AMIN  SHILPA R  DALWADI  SHREYA  SHANTILAL  BANKER  SHUBHANGINI  KOSTA  SHUCHI  RASHMIRATHI  JOSHI  SIDDARAM  SHIVAJI SARATE  SNEHA  ASHVINKUMAR  PADHIAR  SNEHAL  JATINKUMAR  BHATT  SONAL  PRAVINBHAI  RAMI  SUJALKUMAR  VINODKUMAR  DADHANIYA  SWATI  SURESHCHAND  RA PATEL  SWENI  ATULKUMAR  SHAH  TRUSHA  RONAKKUMAR  PATEL  TRUSHIT  KIRTIKUMAR  UPADHYAYA  TUSHAR  GUNVANTRAY  MEHTA  UMANG  HARISHCHANDR  A SHA












     264  265   266  267  268   269  270   271  272   273   274    275   276   277   278   279    280   281   282]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





     30-06-2018  --  --  18-10-2019  --  --  --  --   --    --    --    13-06-2020  --  --  --  --    --    --    --







     02-08-2014  11-12-2013  01-01-2009  01-02-2016  01-04-2016  16-01-2012  01-02-2016  06-07-2015  06-11-2000  20-05-2015  01-01-2014  01-01-2014  11-03-2013  27-07-2010  05-02-2014  23-06-2014  27-12-2012  23-07-2011  01-07-2006










     No     Yes   Yes  No    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   No    Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes






     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes







     69     92    139  61    52    112   79    129    250   309   81    107   94     144  120   74    110   119   238





     M.Sc.  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  MPT(Physio)  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Sc.







     Male   Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male







     Other  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor








     29     35    33   28    28    35    31    34     44    47    29    31    32     37  35     31    31    32    44
     URVESHKUMAR  SUNILKUMAR  SONI  VAIBHAV  KIRITKUMAR  PATEL  VAISHALI  HARDIK KORIA  VALA  VISHWAKUMARI  TIKENDRASINGH  VANDITABEN  SANATKUMAR  SONI  VIBHABEN  NARENDRABHAI  PARMAR  VIDHI  VINODCHANDRA  THAKAR  VIJAY  MAHENDRABHAI  MAKWANA  VIJAYKUMAR  PREMJIBHAI  CHAUDHARY  VIJAYKUMAR  RAMANLAL  PANCHAL  VIKAS  HASMUKHBHAI  PANCHAL  VINAY  PRAGJIBHAI  VIRADIA  VINEETHA  RAVINDRAN  NAIR  VIPIN  VAGERIYA  VIPUL  HARSHADBHAI  VYAS  VIRAL  DHIRAJLAL  PANARA  VISHAL  PARBA












     283    284   285  286   287   288   289   290    291   292   293   294   295    296  297   298   299   300   301]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                                                    30-11-2019      31-12-2019  03-08-2019                23-07-2020


     --     --    --   --    --    --   --    --         --    --        --       --     --    --    --         --



     16-08-2016  01-02-2017  01-08-2014  23-07-2011  25-06-2018  01-09-2018  12-11-2018  16-07-2018  05-07-2018  01-08-2018  01-08-2017  02-08-2018  15-07-2016  10-08-2018  01-09-2018  05-07-2018  14-11-2018  01-08-2018  12-11-2018  07-10-2015









     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   No   Yes   Yes  No   Yes  No  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  No    Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   No   No    No    No   No    Yes  No   Yes  No  No     No    No    No   No    Yes







     65     74    69   109   74    89   36    64    87   64    96   27   54   27  82     78    25    37   25    549



     MPT(Physio)  Master of  Optometry  M.Tech  M.Tech  B.E  M. Pharm  M.Sc.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  M.S  MPT(Physio)  M. Pharm  M.Tech  B.Sc.  Ph.D  B.Sc.  Ph.D








     Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male






     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Other  Professor










     32     30    30   35    27    34   26    37    31   29    31   26   35   26  33     30    23    31   23    66



     YASHREE  THAKORBHAI  PATEL  YOGESH  RAVJIBHAI  VAGHELA  YOGESH  SURESH TIWARI  ZANKHAN  CHANDRAKANT  SONARA  AJAY  GANPATBHAI  PRAJAPATI  ALKESHKUMAR  KIRITBHAI PATEL  ANGELINABEN  ARVINDBHAI  MAKWANA  ANOOP  RAVINDRANATH  MARKANDE  DHARA NARESH  JAJAL  DIPAKKUMAR  JIVRAJBHAI  RAMOLIYA  DWEEPNA  GARG  EKTABEN  ATULBHAI SONI  FORAM NILESH  PATHAK  GAURAVGIRI  HARIGIRI GOSAI  HARDIK  MUKESHKUMAR  KORIA  HEMAL  SANJAYKUMAR  PAREKH  HEMALIBEN  JITENDRABHAI  PANCHAL  JANK









     302    303   304  305   306   307  308   309   310  311   312  313  314  315  316   317   318   319  320   321]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





                     30-09-2019  13-02-2020  09-09-2019  31-07-2020                 14-08-2019  31-07-2020   10-06-2020


     --     --  --           --   --               --   --    --     --    --   --               --    --          --



     01-08-2018  25-07-2018  02-07-2018  01-08-2018  12-11-2018  11-08-2018  16-08-2018  12-11-2018  25-06-2018  01-06-2018  01-05-2018  25-10-2017  12-11-2018  14-07-2017  15-05-2018  12-11-2018  12-11-2018  19-07-2017  27-08-2018  11-06-2018  04-07-2018









     Yes    Yes  Yes  No  No  Yes  Yes  No   No    Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  No    No    Yes   Yes   No    Yes







     Yes    No  No   No   Yes  Yes  No  No   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    No    Yes  Yes  No    No    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes






     111    60  49   107  48  125  51  42    38    30   504   120    134   63   54  25     25    51    193   47    106







     Ph.D   M.E.  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  M.E.  M. Pharm  M.Tech  Ph.D  B.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.






     Male   Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female





     Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     33     28  27   42   28  33  27   27    26    26   67    30     38    29   35  26     26    26    40    30    32



     KAMESH  VISWANATHAN  BASKARAN  KHUSHI ANAND  PATEL  KRISHNA  PATEL  MAHENDRA  SEERVI  MAHESH CHAND  MANDAR DILIP  KULKARNI  MANNA  DEBNATH  MEET  ARVINDBHAI  PATEL  MICHELE  JAYKANT  MISTRY  MITVA MAUNIL  THAKKAR  PANKAJ  SHANTILAL  JOSHI  PARTH  NAVINCHANDRA  GOEL  PAYALBEN  PURSHOTTAMBH  AI CHAUHAN  PHENILKUMAR  PRAKASH BUCH  PRATHYAKSH  JANARDHANAN  PRITIKSHA  CHIRAG  SHARMA  PRIYANKABEN  GOVINDBHAI  TALPADA  RADHIKA  BHARATBHAI  PATEL  RAJENDRA  MULJIBHAI  KOTADI









     322    323  324  325  326  327  328  329  330  331  332  333    334   335  336  337   338   339   340   341   342]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





     25-09-2019  --  --  10-07-2019  --  --  --  --  --   --     --    --    --    --   --   --    --   --    --







     21-07-2017  02-07-2018  25-07-2018  02-07-2018  24-07-2018  07-12-2017  01-09-2018  01-09-2018  01-09-2018  26-07-2018  23-07-2018  12-11-2018  21-07-2018  22-10-2018  14-05-2018  15-10-2018  01-12-2018  26-12-2018  24-06-2019










     No     Yes   Yes   No   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes






     Yes    No    No    No   No    Yes   No   No    No    No     No    Yes   No    No   Yes  No    No   Yes   Yes







     80     44    28    50   40    95    61   128   178   39     178   25    74    404  115  57    48   54    17


            M.Sc.(Nursing)               MPT(Physio)                                    MPT(Physio)


     M.E.         M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D    Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.  M.E.  B.Sc.   Ph.D  Ph.D  M. Pharm  MCA





     Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female






     Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Associate  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     29     27    25    27   28    30    29   33    35    26     38    26    27    63   35   35    32   27    23


       ARVINDBHAI  ARVINDBHAI  ATUFAALI  IMDADALI  SAMARTH  SHRADDHA  PARESHKUMAR  DEVENDRABHAI  SUMAM  SUNNY  SWAYAMPRAKA  SH KANTILAL  AMRUTLAL  VIDHIBEN  TUSHARKUMAR  YOGESHWARI  FAKIRBHAI  ANKITKUMAR  SUNILBHAI  CHRISTIAN  BHARGAV  BHARATBHAI  SHOBHANA  FARZANA  SHIPRAA  SHAH  VANARAJSINH  JASHAVANTSINH  LALJIBHAI DESAI  KAMLESHBHAI  HARSHADBHAI

     RIMA  PITRODA  RUTVI  THAKOR  SAIYED  BHATIA  VYAS  SHWETA  DABHI  PATEL  TAPAN  PATEL  PANDYA  PATEL  MUNEER  SOLANKI  JAGRUTI  NIKUNJ  PAREKH  RAJVI  YADAV







     343    344   345   346  347   348   349  350   351   352    353   354   355   356  357  358   359  360   361]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular





               30-06-2020  30-11-2019  06-07-2020                          15-11-2019


     --   --             --    --         --   --    --    --   --   --         --    --    --    --    --   --



     24-06-2019  01-01-2019  01-01-2019  17-12-2018  17-06-2019  10-01-2019  27-12-2018  27-12-2018  01-01-2019  01-01-2019  21-01-2019  01-05-2019  28-09-2017  12-11-2018  17-06-2019  10-06-2019  11-06-2019  12-06-2019  13-06-2019  17-06-2019









     Yes  Yes  No   No   Yes   Yes   No   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   No   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes







     Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes







     28   101  74   28   17    23    23   23   22    22    22   220  38    24   17    121   30    17    27   124




     M. Pharm  M.A  M.Ed  M.Sc.  MBA  M. Phil  BPT  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  BPT  Ph.D  B.Sc.  B.Sc.  B.Sc.  M.E.  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.







     Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male






     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Other  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Associate  Professor  Other  Other  Other  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     25   31   32   24   24    33    24   24   28    27    24   40   24    22   24    33    28    25    26   32
     RICHA RAKESH  DAVE  RADHIKA  BHAT  ISHAN VINAY  PANDYA  ANKIT BABUBHAI  KOTHIYA  KESHA  JIGNESHKUMAR  PATEL  PRAGNESHKUM  AR ROHITBHAI  MAKWANA  DAMINI  VINOD  PATEL  PANKTI ASHOK  PATEL  SONALBEN  HARSHADBHAI  RATHOD  FORUM  DHIRENKUMAR  SHROFF  SONI ARCHI  DILIPBHAI  ATANU  BANERJEE  PRIYANCY  DHRUPALKUMAR  PATEL  NIRALIBEN  KIRITBHAI PATEL  SHREYASKUMAR  HEMANTBHAI  PATEL  BHAVIKABEN  NANDANKUMAR  PATEL  DRASHTI  MOHANLAL  GARADHARIA  SHIVAM  HARSHADKUMA  R RIBADI












     362  363  364  365  366   367   368  369  370   371   372  373  374   375  376   377   378   379   380  381]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Visiting





                                                                   18-12-2019                         24-10-2019  31-10-2019


     --     --    --    --    --    --     --    --    --    --           --  --     --    --   --             --  --



     20-06-2019  20-06-2019  20-06-2019  24-06-2019  24-06-2019  24-06-2019  10-06-2019  11-06-2019  11-06-2019  17-06-2019  24-06-2019  21-08-2017  11-10-2018  01-04-2019  05-03-2001  23-06-2016  02-05-2018  01-08-2018  07-11-2016  01-07-2015









     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   No     Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   No   No  Yes  Yes







     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes







     81     124   52    27    17    30     45    51    81    61    82     73  25     25    236  135   51   463  360  132






     M.E.   M.E.  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Sc.  B.Sc.  M.Sc.  Ph.D  MBA  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  Ph.D  MBA





     Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male






     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     30     34    28    26    24    26     26    27    32    29    31     30  24     25    89   34    30   65  59  32

       ANANTKUMAR  VIJAYKUMAR  BHUPENDRASIN  H VAGHELA  AISHWARIYA  SURESHKUMAR  BUDHRANI  AKASHKUMAR  RAVINDRABHAI  PUSHPAKANT  CHAUDHARI  ASHOKKUMAR  MIKINBHAI  RAKESHBHAI  REKHABEN  KARANGIYA  BHARATBHAI  RAMJIBHAI  SARKHEDI  DOLLY  SHARMA  DHIRUBHAI  JIGNESHKUMAR  DR SHIVPRASAD  DIIPTI  PANIA  PARESH SHAH  HARDIK S SHAH


     RIMA  PATEL  HARSHIL  JOSHI  CHINTAL  UPENDRA  RAVAL  PRIYALBA  PATEL  AAYUSHI  RUCHITA  MACWAN  PATEL  KARABHAI  VASVIBEN  PARMAR  FORAM  SHELAT  KOSTA  DIVYANG  VAIJNATH  PUROHIT  SULABHA  NATRAJ







     382    383   384   385   386   387    388   389   390   391   392    393  394   395   396  397   398  399  400  401]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[Visiting  Visiting  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular





                             03-05-2020


     --   --   --    --  --       --    --     --     --    --      --    --    --     --    --    --   --   --



     01-11-2017  01-11-2017  02-03-2020  04-03-2017  23-07-2012  12-10-2018  18-09-2017  21-11-2017  16-05-2018  16-05-2018  08-07-2019  15-07-2019  01-01-2020  01-10-2019  03-02-2020  15-07-2019  26-08-2019  02-03-2020  15-07-2019









     Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  No  Yes  Yes    Yes    Yes   Yes     Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes







     Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   No      No    No    No     No    No    No   No   No






     209  119  5     504  126  48  53   70     47     68    38      40    246   112    102   25    12   68   99







     M.D  M.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  MSc(IT)  Ph.D  MSc(IT)  MCA  MCA  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  MBA  M.A  Ph.D  M.Sc.






     Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male





     Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Assistant  Professor  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     43   33   30    65  33  29   28    39     27     30    26      29    44    32     33    24    39   56   31



     SANJAY K  GUPTA  UTSAV PAREKH  NILESH  OMPRAKASH  PANDEY  DIPAK S VYAS  MINAL NIRAV  SHAH  VIKAS ROHIT  KEYURBHAI  PIYUSHBHAI  PATEL  MITESHKUMAR  HARISHBHAI  PATEL  KRUPESHKUMA  R  JAYENDRAKUMA  R PATEL  NEEL  SHAILESHBHAI  PATEL  BHARGAV  RAJABABUSHIVJ  ANARDANPRASA  D VYAS  PARTHIV  ANIRUDDHBHAI  PATEL  SHAILESH  BABUBHAI  KHANT  ASHISH  DHIRUBHAI  PATEL  ADILKUMAR  SANATKUMAR  PATEL  AARZOOBEN  SALIMBHAI  VHORA  ANILA  MALGAONKAR  JIGNASU R  YAGNIK  PURVAKKUMAR









     402  403  404   405  406  407  408  409   410    411   412     413   414   415    416   417   418  419  420]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular









     --     --  --   --    --     --    --   --  --  --    --    --    --     --    --    --   --   --  --      --



     02-09-2019  02-02-2019  09-09-2019  30-09-2019  12-03-2020  19-08-2019  26-08-2019  26-08-2019  02-09-2019  04-07-2019  01-07-2019  02-03-2020  01-07-2019  22-07-2019  23-08-2019  05-07-2019  05-07-2019  13-08-2019  13-08-2019  20-08-2019









     Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes







     No     No  No   No    No     No    No   No  No  Yes   No    No    No     No    No    No   No   No  No      No







     11     11  92   11    38     23    124  53  50  36    23    23    38     50    105   25   25   22  12      12



     MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  B.Sc.








     Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male






     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Lecturer  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other










     24     26  33   25    37     25    38   30  36  28    26    33    27     27    35    25   25   25  23      23

       BHASKARBHAI  SHIKHA JAYESH  RAHUL TIWARI  DIXA KHIMJIBHAI  CHANDRAVADIY  LAXMIKANT  PARSHOTTAMBH  SHALINI JOSHI  MANISH TRIVEDI  SWAPAN DEEP  DHANOPIA  JANARDAN  JAYANTIBHAI  GAURANGKUMA  R KHODABHAI  NIRMALKUMAR  DEEPKUMAR  RAMESHBHAI  KOTHADIYA  ANVARHUSEN  MUKUNDBHAI  SANTOSH OJHA  KARAN SITARAM  MOHAMMAD  AKHLAQUE  MOHAMMAD  SAMI AHMAD  RAJNANDINI  DHANNALAL

     AMEE  PAREKH  SHAH  A  GAURAV  SOLANKI  ISHITA  AI SHAH  BHARVAD  PATEL  DIPANJAN  DEY  NISHAT  SHAIKH  MADHAV  AJWALIA  ANUPAM  NIRAULA  MORJE  PATIDAR








     421    422  423  424  425    426   427  428  429  430  431  432   433    434   435   436  437  438  439    440]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[Regular  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting





     30-06-2020  --  --  --  30-06-2020  --







     01-07-2019  05-11-2019  17-06-2019  08-01-2020  16-01-2019  23-06-2020










     No   Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes






     No   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes







     13   362  132  66  86  84






     Ph.D  Ph.D  MD  M.D  MD  M. Phil






     Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female





     Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor  Other  Other  Assistant  Professor  Assistant  Professor










     54   56   34  30  28   31

     CHAKRADHAR  IYYUNNI  Dr Hemant Tiwari  Dr Maulik Shah  Paresh Ashokbhai  Varsat  Mona Megha  Mukshita Y  Dharangadhra











     441  442  443  444  445  446]]></page></pages></Search>