<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="27"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[No. of students  who are not  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  No. of students selected for Higher  Studies  No. of students selected for Higher  Studies



                         2015-16                        475  1009  289                  171  230  270               342

                                            No. of students  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  from the Private  Bodies



                             -  -   -                   1    2    1              Median salary of  placed graduates(Amount in  Rs.)  130000(One lakh  Thirty Thousand)  180000(One lakh  eighty thousand)  180000(One Lakh  Eighty Thousand)  Median salary of  placed graduates(Amount in  Rs.)  240000(Two lakh Forty

                                            No. of students  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  from Institution  Funds  Thousand)


                         2016-17                        21   32   8


                                            No. of students  receiving full  tuition fee  reimbursement  from the State  and Central  Government  No. of students  placed  No. of students  placed


                             -  -   -                   30   241  45                    39   24   51                589




                         2017-18            Socially  Challenged  (SC+ST+OBC  Including male  & female)  209  391  178  No. of students  graduating in minimum stipulated  time  No. of students  graduating in minimum stipulated  time  1048
      National Institutional Ranking Framework


                                            Economically  Backward  (Including male  & female)  318  893  165  Academic Year  Academic Year
                                1240                                                    286  352  412
                             -      -

        Ministry of Education Government of India Welcome to Data Capturing System: OVERALL  2018-19  Outside  Country  (Including male  & female)  41  2018-19  2019-20  2020-21  2018-19









                                            Outside State  (Including male  & female)  43  69  25  0  0  0          157
                             540  1400  -               4         1              No. of students  admitted through  Lateral entry  No. of students  admitted through  Lateral entry





                         2019-20            Within State  (Including male  & female)  Academic Year         Academic Year
                 Institute Name: Charotar University of Science & Technology [IR-O-U-0128]




                             570  1400  684             1536  5170  1017                2017-18  2018-19  2019-20   2016-17
                                            Total Students  1583  5280  1043     No. of first year students admitted in  the year  No. of first year students admitted in  the year




                         2020-21         Total Actual Student Strength (Program(s) Offered by Your Institution)  No. of Female  Students  716  1602  557  UG [3 Years Program(s)]: Placement & higher studies for previous 3 years  317  384  434 UG [4 Years Program(s)]: Placement & higher studies for previous 3 years  959

               Submitted Institute Data for NIRF'2022'  Sanctioned (Approved) Intake  Academic Year  540 UG [3 Years Program(s)]  1370 UG [4 Years Program(s)]  676 PG [2 Year Program(s)]  No. of Male (All programs  Students of all years)  867 UG [3 Years  Program(s)]  3678 UG [4 Years  Program(s)]  486 PG [2 Year  Program(s)]  Placement & Higher Studies  No. of first year Academic Year students intake in the  year  300 2016-17  360 2017-18  540 2018-19  No. of first year]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[No. of students selected for Higher  Studies




     258  400             25     46  70



     310000(Three lakh  Ten Thousand)  300000(Three lakh)  Median salary of  placed graduates(Amount in  Rs.)  225000(Two lakh  Twenty Five  Thousand)  240000(Two lakh Forty  Thousand)  230000(Two lakh  Thirty Thousand)  2018-19  0








                   No. of students  placed         Total Students   5  23            2018-19




     468  619             354    274  312


                   No. of students graduating in minimum  stipulated time




     956  1029                                                  2019-20







     2019-20  2020-21     579    556  465      Ph.D (Student pursuing doctoral program till 2020-21 Students admitted in the academic year 2020-21 should not be entered here.)  77  96 No. of Ph.D students graduated (including Integrated Ph.D)  7  28 PG (Student pursuing MD/MS/DNB program till 2020-21 Students admitted in the academic year 2021 - 22 should not be entered here)  No. of students Graduating in PG (MD/MS/DNB) program  0  Yes









                   Academic Year                                2020-21       Number of students pursuing PG (MD/MS/DNB) program  2019-20
     143  134






                PG [2 Years Program(s)]: Placement & higher studies for previous 3 years
     2017-18  2018-19     2018-19  2019-20  2020-21



                   No. of first year students admitted in  the year  6  22              0





     923  1114            666    570  485


                   No. of first year students intake in the  year



     1055  1240           794    728  684                                            2020-21     1. Does all programs/courses were completed on time.



                   Academic Year            Ph.D Student Details                              Online Education


     2016-17  2017-18     2017-18  2018-19  2019-20   Full Time  Part Time  Full Time  Part Time  0]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[and Learning Management Systems including Microsoft Team, Moodle, Google Classroom, Google Meet, Zoom, Webex etc. were
                     inviting experts. Charusat has invested a tremendous amount to procure high-end computer machines which may not be available
                   laboratory sessions, Individual and group assignments, group discussions, simulations, case studies, seminars and workshops by
                                      the Turnitin software. End-semester theory examinations were also taken online for most of the students. The teachers had taken
                                   The online education and learning platforms not only aided the syllabus completion but also facilitated in continuous evaluation of
                  A representative list of teaching approaches to ensure effective learning includes case scenario-based practicals, tutorials, virtual
                        CHARUSAT took initiative and provided remote desktop of lab computers to complete their experimentation. In addition, students
            They evolved various approaches of teaching like making animated videos, making pre-recorded video lectures, arranging online
              expert sessions, conducting webinars and even started with their own YouTube channel too. Many pre-recorded audio and video
                                    students through quizzes, assignments, and video conferencing-based discussions. Plagiarism checking has been done through
                         are mentored and encouraged to undertake MOOCs. University also has NPTEL Local chapter. University had received the free
     During and post-lockdown due to COVID-19, to continue the teaching and learning of the students at home, various online tools
        utilized by the faculty members to create effective and virtual classroom environment. Almost all the faculty members voluntarily
                               In addition, resources for learning in the form of recorded videos, notes, e-books, videos on practical skills, and other reference
          participated in various workshops and training programs to sharpen their skills in conducting courses through online modes.
                          9491 licenses of Coursera. These licenses are used to provide free courses to the students to learn additional topics of the
                      at home. In pandemic situation, there was a challenge to carry out memory and compute hungry experiments by students.
                                                        Total no. of credits transferred to transcript  2018-19  Utilised Amount  15797904 (One crore fifty seven lakhs ninety seven thousand 21883712 (Two crore eighteen lakhs eighty three thousand 1277315 (Twelve lakhs seventy seven thousand three hundred 24261936 (Two crore forty two lakhs sixty one thousand nine
                                             Students were trained and their feedbacks were taken to make the online mode of teaching, learning and evaluation more
                                           Issues faced by students related to online teaching, learning and evaluation are diligently addressed by faculty members.
                                       the mock examination with students to get them familiar with the online examination. Examinations have both MCQ and
               sessions are now available to the students to view as per their convenience and to learn at their own pace.
                                              effective. Online parents-teacher meetings were also conducted to obtain their feedback and suggestions.
                                materials were shared by all faculty members. For needy students, library books were delivered at home.
                            courses offered. Doubt clearing session was an integral part of the learning.
                                                             58  8  108  28                    nine hundred four)  seven hundred twelve)  fifteen)  hundred thirty six)







                                                          to the transcript Total no. of online courses which have credit transferred  2019-20  Utilised Amount  14531669 (One crore forty five lakhs thirty one thousand six 12893238 (One crore twenty eight lakhs ninety three thousand 1844692 (Eighteen lakhs forty four thousand six hundred ninety 76140825 (Seven crore sixty one lakhs forty thousand eight





                                        descriptive components.  0  0  29  4  54  14  4   Annual Capital Expenditure on Academic Activities and Resources (excluding expenditure on buildings)  hundred sixty nine)  two hundred thirty eight)  two)  hundred twenty five)















                                                          transferred to transcript No. of students offered online courses which have credit  2020-21  Utilised Amount  14170720 (One crore forty one lakhs seventy thousand seven 55729213 (Five crore fifty seven lakhs twenty nine thousand 1540250 (Fifteen lakhs forty thousand two hundred fifty) 11131299 (One crore eleven lakhs thirty one thousand two










                                                                                               hundred twenty)  two hundred thirteen)  hundred ninety nine)



     2. Measures taken to complete the syllabus of courses and programs.
                                                             29  4  22  11 5. No. of courses developed and available online on Swayam platform  by your institution faculty Financial Resources: Utilised Amount for the Capital expenditure for previous 3 years  Financial Resources: Utilised Amount for the Operational expenditure for previous 3 years
                                                 3. The period of delay in completion of syllabus (in months).
                                                     4. The period of delay in conducting exams (in months).  Portal Name  Swayam  Udemy  Coursera  Other  Academic Year  Library  New Equipment for Laboratories  Engineering Workshops Other expenditure on creation of Capital Assets (excluding expenditure on Land and Building)]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[2018-19  Utilised Amount  380929793 (Thirty eight crore nine lakhs twenty nine thousand 257064165 (Twenty five crore seventy lakhs sixty four 5663720 (Fifty six lakhs sixty three thousand seven hundred  2018  2018-19  Eighty five lakhs five thousand three hundred thirty four  2018-19  Sixty five lakhs one thousand nine hundred twenty nine  2018-19

                 seven hundred ninety three)  thousand one hundred sixty five)  twenty)  2  1  21  9  8505334  46  22  6501929  1  28  1484000  Fourteen Lakhs Eighty Four Thousand





















     2019-20  Utilised Amount  406457152 (Forty crore sixty four lakhs fifty seven thousand 291589402 (Twenty nine crore fifteen lakhs eighty nine 4839047 (Forty eight lakhs thirty nine thousand forty seven)  2019  2019-20  Seventy one lakhs eighty five thousand seven hundred sixty  2019-20  Eighty five lakhs twenty eight thousand five hundred sixty three  2019-20  Twelve Lakhs Sixty Thousand






            Annual Operational Expenditure  one hundred fifty two)  thousand four hundred two)  0  1  18  8  7185768  eight  37  34  8528563  1  28  1260000















                 thousand four hundred seventy eight)  thousand one hundred forty four)  1  0  27  9  10708645  20  30  7724781  eighty one  2  41  2685000  Twenty Six Lakhs Eighty Five Thousand
     2020-21  Utilised Amount  422924478 (Forty two crore twenty nine lakhs twenty four 489499144 (Forty eight crore ninety four lakhs ninety nine  2642043 (Twenty six lakhs forty two thousand forty three)  2020  2020-21  One crore seventy lakhs eight thousand six hundred forty five  2020-21  Seventy seven lakhs twenty four thousand seven hundred  2020-21





















                Salaries (Teaching and Non Teaching staff)  Seminars/Conferences/Workshops  IPR  No. of Patents Published  No. of Patents Granted  Sponsored Research Details  Total no. of Sponsored Projects  Total no. of Funding Agencies Total Amount Received (Amount in Rupees)  Amount Received in Words  Consultancy Project Details  Total no. of Consultancy Projects  Total no. of Client Organizations Total Amount Received (Amount in Rupees)  Amount Received in Words  Deve
     Academic Year  Maintenance of Academic Infrastructure or consumables and other running expenditures(excluding maintenance of hostels and allied services,rent of the building, depreciation cost, etc)  Calendar year  Financial Year  Financial Year  Executive Development Program/Management Development Programs  Financial Year Total no. of Executive Development Programs/ Management  Total Annual Earnings (Amount in Rupees)(Excluding Lodging]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Association type  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular








                                                         Leaving Date



                                             CGPA            --     --    --    --   --    --  --    --  --  --   --



                                                         Joining Date  15-07-2019  05-06-2017  18-07-2011  01-02-2016  08-08-2013  09-03-2009  18-01-2016  14-03-2009  19-10-2016  30-10-2006  01-02-2016









                                                3.11     Currently working  with institution?  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes



           Yes, more than 80% of the buildings  Yes, more than 80% of the buildings  Experience (In  Months)  37  59  147  156  130  152  78  254  83  178  100










                                         YES
                                             Valid upto  Qualification
              Yes
                                 NO
                                                             MBA    Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  B.Sc.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech
              2. Do your institution have provision for walking aids, including wheelchairs and transportation from one building to another for


                                                         Gender



                                                24-05-2021   Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male


                                                         Designation      Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor
                   3. Do your institution buildings have specially designed toilets for handicapped students?

                                                             Other  Other                            Other

        PCS Facilities: Facilities of physically challenged students


                                                         Age  25    29    35    37   36    41  29    43  29  38   31


           1. Do your institution buildings have Lifts/Ramps?  handicapped students?  Accreditation  NBA Accreditation 1.Does your institute have a valid NBA Accreditation?  NAAC Accreditation 1. Does your institute have a valid NAAC Accreditation?  25-05-2016  Faculty Details  Name  Srno  AARZOOBEN  1  MAHAMADASHIF  SHEKH  ALKESHBHAI  2  BHIKHABHAI  PATEL  ABHILASH  3  MAHESHKUMAR  SHUKLA  ABHISHEK  4  SWARNKAR  ABHISHEK  5  NATHALAL  DADHANIA  ADITI D BUCH  6  AKASH  7
                                             Valid from]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular










     --     --  --     --  --     --  --     --    --   --    --   --    --    --  --    --    --    --    --    --



     01-04-2001  11-07-2002  22-06-2006  13-03-2007  17-05-2013  01-04-2017  16-01-2012  08-06-2010  01-04-2016  05-07-2017  25-08-2011  04-08-2016  19-06-2014  18-11-2010  01-02-2016  01-12-2016  01-10-2015  23-07-2002  13-03-2007  04-09-2017










     Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes








     241    229  192   173  116   124  157   163   83   132   134  77    111   514  132  119   109   229   173   74







     Ph.D   Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.E.  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  MCA  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female



     Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor













     43     40  37     36  33     43  37     37    31   32    35   30    33    74  35    36    31    42    38    31

       PRAVINCHANDRA  AMIT RAMANLAL  AMITKUMAR  JAYDEVBHAI  AMITKUMAR  VINUBHAI PATEL  AMRINBANU MOHAMMADHANIF  ANAMIKA SANJAY  PURSHOTAMBHAI  ANIL SURESH  CHAND SHARMA  ANILKUMAR  ANIRUDDHKUMAR GOVARDHANDAS  ANJALI PUSHKAR  JAYESHKUMAR  WANKAWALA  HARSADBHAI  ARABINDA  RAY  JAYPRAKASH  HARISHKUMAR  RASESHKUMAR  JIGNESHKUMAR  PINALKUMAR  ARTEE  TYAGI



     AMIT  GANATRA  THAKKAR  NAYAK  SHAIKH  JHA  ANAND  PATEL  PATIDAR  FATANIYA  TIWARI  ANKIT  ANKUR  PATEL  ARPAN  PANDYA  ARPAN  DESAI  ARPIT  TRIVEDI  ARPITA  SHAH  ARPITA  PATEL









     12     13  14     15  16     17  18     19    20   21    22   23    24    25  26    27    28    29    30    31]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                                                                                     27-02-2021  29-01-2021


     --     --  --     --    --  --  --    --    --     --    --    --    --   --               --  --  --   --    --



     09-07-2010  03-07-2017  17-12-2008  01-07-2015  24-04-2007  01-09-2018  12-11-2018  16-07-2018  12-11-2018  24-06-2019  24-06-2019  10-06-2019  01-10-2019  03-02-2020  26-08-2019  02-09-2019  05-07-2019  01-05-2019  06-05-2005  11-04-2011  17-01-2011










     Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   No   No    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes








     339    467  204   486   206  110  48  125   43     29    42    57    124  114   24   23    37  232  254  145  127







     B.Sc.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M. Pharm  M.Sc.  Ph.D  M.Sc.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.A  MPT(Physio)  M.Sc.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech






     Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male



                Assistant Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor



     Other  Professor    Chancellor  Lecturer    Lecturer                                                 Chancellor









     58     66  40     63    43  35  27    38    27     25    27    27    33   34    40   25    26  41  52   35    33
       PRABHASHANKAR  BHULABHAI PATEL  ASHWINKUMAR  BHANUPRASAD  ASHWINKUMAR DHULABHAI PATEL  ANJANA   KOTHARI  ALKESHKUMAR  KIRITBHAI PATEL  ANGELINABEN  RAVINDRANATH  ANKITKUMAR  SURESHKUMAR  AKASHKUMAR  RAVINDRABHAI  PUSHPAKANT  DHIRUBHAI PATEL  SANATKUMAR  MALGAONKAR  BHASKARBHAI  ANUPAM NIRAULA  ATANU  BANERJEE  ATUL MANUBHAI  BHARATKUMAR  AXAT VIJAYKUMAR



     ARUNA  JANI  ARVINDBHAI  MAKWANA  ARVINDBHAI  MAKWANA  ANOOP  MARKANDE  SUNILBHAI  CHRISTIAN  AISHWARIYA  BUDHRANI  PATEL  AAYUSHI  CHAUDHARI  ASHISH  ADILKUMAR  PATEL  ANILA  AMEE  PAREKH  PATEL  AVANI  CHOKSI  PATEL










     32     33  34     35    36  37  38    39    40     41    42    43    44   45    46   47    48  49  50   51    52]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






            04-01-2021


     --         --     --    --    --   --    --    --   --    --  --  --     --    --   --  --      --    --    --



     29-04-2009  05-07-2018  16-04-2004  19-01-2013  16-01-2017  11-08-2005  05-07-2018  01-02-2016  01-02-2008  01-01-2013  27-04-2004  25-11-2019  21-07-2018  10-06-2019  13-06-2019  17-06-2019  08-07-2019  18-06-2019  02-08-2010  01-04-2016










     Yes    No  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes








     179    128  228   133   164   201  152   118   271  134   208  40  86    133   39   136  50     24    133   89



            M.Sc.(Nursing)              M.Sc.(Nursing)                                                           M.Sc.(Nursing)


     Ph.D       Ph.D   M.E.  Ph.D  M.E.       MBA   Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  M.E.  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  MCA  MCA  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male



     Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Lecturer  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor













     40     38  41     33    36    38   39    34    50   34    41  26  28     34    27   33  27      24    33    30

     BALAGANAPATHY MURUGANANTHAN  M  BAPU  KHODNAPUR  BHASKAR  KANAIYALAL  PANDYA  BHAVIN  HARESHKUMAR  MEHTA  BHAVTOSH  ANILKUMAR  KIKANI  BIMAL HARIVADAN  PATEL  BINAL  DHARMINKUMAR  JOSHI  BINITKUMAR  NAINESHBHAI  PATEL  BRAGADISH D  IYER  BRIJESH  LAXMANBHAI  KUNDALIYA  BRIJESH N SHAH  ATUFAALI IMDADALI SAIYAD  BHARGAV  BHARATBHAI  SHOBHANA  BHAVIKABEN  NANDANKUMAR  PATEL  BINAL SAGAR  KAKA  CHANDRASHEKHA R SURESH PAWAR  BHARGAV RAJABABUSHIVJA  NARDANPRASAD  VYAS  DIP














     53     54  55     56    57    58   59    60    61   62    63  64  65     66    67   68  69      70    71    72]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                                                                                            06-07-2020


     --     --    --    --   --   --    --   --  --   --   --    --   --   --   --    --         --   --    --    --



     20-07-2015  10-10-2011  24-07-2007  04-06-2020  25-08-2011  01-06-2015  23-06-2014  29-10-2018  13-10-2008  16-08-2004  01-09-2010  23-06-2014  01-10-2015  05-08-2003  04-10-2017  01-08-2019  27-12-2018  20-06-2019  01-07-2019  01-04-2016  07-07-2014










     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   No   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes








     151    200   277   97   140  91    120  68  188  211  150   101  141  216  64    76    30   64   50    119   120



                             M.Sc.(Nursing)


     Ph.D   Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Sc.     M.E.  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  MCA  M.E.  Ph.D  M.E.  BPT  M.E.  M.E.  MCA  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male


     Associate Professor  Associate Professor  Associate Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Lecturer  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor














     41     45    45    31   36   32    32   36  36   43   36    30   37   38   32    30    25   29   28    32    42
       RAMESHCHANDRA  DARSHANKUMAR  HASMUKHBHAI  DEBAYAN DILIP  KRISHNAMURTHY  GHANSHYAMBHAI  DHARA NRUPAL  DHARA PINKESH  DHARMENDRA TRIKAMLAL PATEL  DHARMENDRASIN H VIRENDRASINH  DHARMESHSINH AJMALSINH DABHI  KIRANBHAI RAVAL  DHAVALKUMAR  AMBALAL BHOI  MAHENDRABHAI  DAMINI  VINOD  UPENDRA RAVAL  BHASKARJYOTI


     CHIRAYU  DESAI  PATEL  DATTATRAYA  GANPATRAO  SUBHEDAR  BAIDYA  DEEPAK  DEVANG  PATEL  DHARA MILAN  PATEL  PATEL  PATEL  CHAUHAN  DHATRI  DIJITKUMAR  PATEL  DIPAKKUMAR  JIVRAJBHAI  RAMOLIYA  PATEL  CHINTAL  DEEPKUMAR  RAMESHBHAI  KOTHADIYA  HARDIK  ISHWARBHAI  PATEL  BORAH











     73     74    75    76   77   78    79   80  81   82   83    84   85   86   87    88    89   90   91    92    93]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                                                                                        31-12-2020  05-10-2020


     --     --    --   --    --   --    --    --  --  --   --   --  --   --   --  --               --  --   --



     01-06-2009  02-08-2010  16-02-2009  01-08-2019  01-04-2016  01-02-2016  08-01-2009  29-04-2009  03-05-2007  18-07-2019  07-02-2008  02-12-2013  01-07-2015  09-01-2017  15-09-2007  29-03-2012  01-12-2016  06-05-2006  09-06-2009  01-01-2009  01-06-2015










     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  No  No  Yes  Yes  Yes








     191    132   150  56    78   73    151   158  187  58  262  125  119  84  182  195  61  268   169  156  125







     Ph.D   M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  M.Sc.  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech







     Male   Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male


     Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Lecturer  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Professor  Lecturer  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     40     33    36   28    31   30    42    38  39  28   47   35  33   30   38  39    32   45    37  34   33


     DHRUVKUMAR  PARESHKUMAR  DAVE  DIPALI  YOGESHBHAI  PATEL  DIPALKUMAR M  PATEL  DIPSI  RAJESHKUMAR  DAVE  DIVYA  JAIN  PACHORI  DIVYESH BHUPENDRABHAI  PATEL  C K SUMESH  MANSI K SONI  FALGUNI AMBALAL  RAVAL  FRANNY JOEL  EMMANUEL  GAJANAN S  PATANGE  GARGI KETUL RAY  GAURANG  ARVINDBHAI  PATEL  GAURAV VILAS  KAPSE  GAYATRI A DAVE  GAYATRIBAHEN  CHHAGANBHAI  PATEL  GLORY JAYESH  WAGHELA  GOVIND  BHASKARBHAI  DAVE  HARDIK P MODI  HARDIK  SUDHIRBHAI  JAYSWAL  HARMISH  GO













     94     95    96   97    98   99    100   101  102  103  104  105  106  107  108  109  110  111  112  113  114]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






     10-05-2021  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  30-01-2021  24-08-2020  30-09-2020  06-08-2020  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --







     01-02-2016  01-04-2016  01-01-2009  01-04-2010  01-09-2008  01-10-2008  01-08-2017  01-09-2018  05-07-2018  14-11-2018  01-01-2019  11-06-2019  20-06-2019  21-08-2017  01-04-2019  30-09-2019  12-03-2020  01-07-2019  02-03-2020  15-07-2019  01-01-2020











     No     Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  No  No   No    No    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes







     75     80    169   184  402  227  108  99  90  37    34    42    136   85  37    23   143   42    35    52    258




            MPT(Physio)                M. Pharm           MPT(Physio)                 MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)

     M.E.         M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  B.Sc.   M.E.  M.E.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.         M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male


     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Lecturer  Assistant Professor  Lecturer  Assistant Professor














     31     32    36    48   61  56  32  34  31    24     28    29    35    31  26    26   38    27    34    30    45





     HARSH  PINAKINBHAI  PATEL  HEMAL MAHENDRAKUMA  R PATEL  HEMANT  NANDLALBHAI  YADAV  NEERAJ  DEVENDRA JAIN  R V UPADHYAY  SEEMA R AMIN  DWEEPNA  GARG  HARDIK  MUKESHKUMAR  KORIA  HEMAL  SANJAYKUMAR  PAREKH  HEMALIBEN  JITENDRABHAI  PANCHAL  FORUM  DHIRENKUMAR  SHROFF  DRASHTI  MOHANLAL  GARADHARIA  HARSHIL  VIJAYKUMAR  JOSHI  DOLLY  SHARMA  FORAM  JIGNESHKUMAR  SHELAT  DIXA KHIMJIBHAI CHANDRAVADIYA  GAURAV  LAXMIKANT  SOLANKI  GAURANGKUMAR  KHODABHAI  PATEL  DIPANJAN









     115    116   117   118  119  120  121  122  123  124  125  126   127   128  129  130  131   132   133   134   135]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                    27-03-2021                                                          16-06-2021


     --   --   --      --    --  --  --  --    --    --   --    --     --    --  --  --      --    --  --   --    --



     02-03-2020  15-07-2019  02-09-2019  09-09-2019  19-08-2019  26-08-2019  26-08-2019  02-09-2019  04-07-2019  21-08-2004  25-09-2017  20-08-2007  18-07-2019  16-07-2012  01-04-2016  17-09-2007  01-06-2011  05-07-2018  04-05-2019  18-01-2016  30-06-2014  16-01-2012  01-01-2009










     Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes








     78   111  23   104  35  136  65  142  48  212   127  168   57     125   94  225  221  71  112  155  90  115  151




               MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)                         M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Master of Optometry  M.Sc.(Nursing)

     Ph.D  M.Sc.       M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D







     Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male


          Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor


     Professor         Lecturer  Lecturer      Professor  Lecturer










     57   32   27   34  26   39  31  37  29    41    36   37    28     34    32  41  39  29  30    36  32   33    34




     JIGNASU R  YAGNIK  PURVAKKUMAR KANTIBHAI PATEL  SHIKHA JAYESH  SHAH  RAHUL TIWARI  ISHITA PARSHOTTAMBHAI  SHAH  SHALINI JOSHI  MANISH TRIVEDI  SWAPAN DEEP  DHANOPIA  JANARDAN  JAYANTIBHAI  BHARVAD  MAYURKUMAR PRAVINCHANDRA  SUTARIA  JALPA HARSHIT  DESAI  JALPA VASHISHTHKUMA  R SUTHAR  JALPABEN  ASHOKBHAI  PRAJAPATI  JALPESH  HARKISHANBHAI  VASA  JAMIN  CHAUHAN  JANKI N THAKKER  JAY KIRITKUMAR  BHAVSAR  JAYDEEP NILESHBHAI DESAI  JAYDEVSINH  DHANRAJ  PARGARA  JAYESH  P










     136  137  138  139  140  141  142  143  144  145  146  147  148   149   150  151  152  153  154  155  156  157  158]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular










     --   --    --     --  --   --  --  --     --    --    --    --    --     --  --     --    --    --    --    --



     04-07-2017  21-03-2007  01-06-2012  09-07-2007  01-02-2008  18-01-2016  01-01-2014  01-08-2001  23-06-2011  13-06-2011  20-06-2011  01-02-2016  13-10-2008  01-08-2011  01-02-2016  22-07-2013  06-08-2018  01-06-2015  23-07-2011  01-12-2018










     Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes








     156  229   154    169  162  85  283  245  147   141   134   80    166    143  87    116   64    118   121   81







     Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D







     Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female


     Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     34   49    37     37  37   29  50  45     41    36    34    30    36     36  34     34    29    33    33    31



     JIMITKUMAR  RATILAL PATEL  JITENDRA  PRABHAKAR  CHAUDHARI  JIVANADHAR  ASHOKKUMAR  JOSHI  KAMLESH V  CHAUHAN  KANANKUMARI GAMANLAL GAMIT  KANCHAL  DAVE  KANUBHAI KHODIDAS PATEL  KARTIKBHAI  SHASHIKANT  PANDYA  KAUSHAL  PRALHADBHAI  PATEL  KAUSHIK  ROHITKUMAR  TRIVEDI  KEYUR  KAMALDASJI  MAHANT  KHUSHBOO  HIRENKUMAR  KAVAR  KILLOL  VISHNUPRASAD  PANDYA  KIRTI JAYANTIBHAI  MAKWANA  KISHAN  PIYUSHBHAI  PATEL  KRUNALKUMAR BHUPENDRABHAI  KACHHIIA  KRUPABEN DHIRENDRAKUMA











     159  160   161    162  163  164  165  166  167  168   169   170   171    172  173   174   175   176   177   178]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular










     --   --   --    --    --     --    --   --    --  --   --     --  --   --   --    --  --  --     --    --    --



     15-09-2015  25-01-2016  01-06-2012  10-05-2007  02-09-2019  18-04-2011  21-12-2007  27-06-2011  01-09-2009  17-05-2013  29-06-2017  02-02-2015  01-04-2016  06-03-2009  26-06-2015  12-12-2007  18-01-2016  18-01-2016  13-08-2019  23-06-2014  01-08-2007










     Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes








     187  97   117   171   108    131   169  134   153  120  91    127  72  166  74    173  100  101  34    110   168




     MPT(Physio)  M.E.  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M. Pharm  M.Tech  M.E.









     Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female



     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     39   33   34    42    34     33    39   34    34  33   35     36  30   37   28    37  32  30     32    33    38



     LOUREMBAM  SURBALA DEVI  MADHAV  NITINBHAI OZA  MAHAMMADSOAIB  MAHEBOOBMIYA  SAIYAD  MANAN  ARUNKUMAR  RAVAL  MANANKUMAR  NARESHKUMAR  SHAH  MANTHAN  SUDHIRBHAI  MANAVADARIA  MARTIN KANTILAL  PARMAR  MAULIK  JASHVANTLAL  SHAH  MAULIK V SHAH  MAYURI  JAMANADAS  POPAT  MEERA  HARDEVSINH  CHUDASAMA  MEGHA JEMIN  DESAI  MEGHA NISHITH  GOHIL  MEHUL MANUBHAI  PATEL  MEHULKUMAR  PRAVINBHAI  KATAKIYA  MIHIR A BHATT  MIHIR SIDDHARTH  MEHTA  MIHIRKUMAR  RAMESHBHAI  PATEL  MILA











     179  180  181   182   183    184   185  186   187  188  189   190  191  192  193  194  195  196  197   198   199]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                           08-05-2021


     --   --   --    --           --    --    --    --    --     --  --     --    --    --   --   --  --     --    --



     19-07-2014  04-02-2014  08-06-2006  02-07-2012  04-10-2019  24-03-2011  01-07-2019  15-07-2011  23-07-2013  01-07-2015  03-11-2011  06-08-2012  25-07-2012  10-07-2017  17-05-2013  29-10-2007  03-09-2010  12-09-2008  01-02-2016  27-12-2012










     Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   No     Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes








     96   121  191   118   60     215   24    136   133   81     526  132   133   193   115  179  163  154   83    130







     Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  MCA  M. Phil  MBA  M. Phil  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  MSc(Mathematics)  Ph.D  M.Tech







     Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male


     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     29   32   38    33    30     41    29    35    35    36     74  36     36    42    34   38   41  36     29    35

     SANNI DILIPBHAI  KAPATEL  PUNIT BABUBHAI  PATEL  PURVI  HARISHKUMAR  PRAJAPATI  RACHANA  SUNILKUMAR  PATEL  RAJANIKANT  BABUBHAI  VANKAR  RAJENDRA  VINUBHAI  SOLANKI  RAJENDRAKUMAR  BABUBHAI  CHAUHAN  RAJESH  KANAYALAL  SADHWANI  RAJESH  VASANTBHAI  SAVALIA  RAJESHKUMAR  VISHNUBHAI  PATEL  RAJNIKANT MULJIBHAI PATEL  RAMESHWARI  MEGHNADSINH  ZALA  RANDHAWA  KAWALJITSINGH  MANSINGH  RASHMIN  BHARATBHAI  PATEL  RAVIKUMAR VIJAYBHAI PATEL  RAVISH JANAKBHAI PATEL  RESHMA G













     200  201  202   203   204    205   206   207   208   209    210  211   212   213   214  215  216  217   218   219]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                                        31-07-2020                       06-10-2020                          09-06-2021


     --     --  --     --    --   --          --    --    --  --    --      --    --     --    --    --            --



     01-05-2004  29-10-2013  01-06-2013  15-07-2010  01-09-2017  01-02-2016  12-11-2018  19-07-2017  27-08-2018  04-07-2018  24-06-2019  24-06-2019  01-01-2019  20-06-2019  11-06-2019  17-06-2019  20-08-2019  05-07-2018  01-02-2016  13-10-2008










     Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   No    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes     No    Yes








     207    178  98    201   90   94    31    63    205   118  29   40   113  93  63     73    24    37      105   173







     Ph.D   M. Phil  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  Ph.D  M.E.  MCA  M. Pharm  M.A  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  B.Sc.  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male


            Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor


     Professor                          Lecturer                                               Other










     39     39  32     43    42   32    27    27    41    33  24    26   32  31   28     30    24    28      32    38





     RITESH  PRAVINBHAI  PATEL  ROBERT JOSEPH  PARMAR  RONAKKUMAR  NATAVARLAL  PATEL  RUCHA  PRADIPKUMAR  DESAI  RUCHI  CHATURVEDI  RUGNESHKUMAR  RAMESHBHAI  PATEL  PRIYANKABEN  GOVINDBHAI  TALPADA  RADHIKA  BHARATBHAI  PATEL  RAJENDRA  MULJIBHAI  KOTADIYA  RENU  KOSHY  RAJVI  HARSHADBHAI  YADAV  RICHA RAKESH  DAVE  RADHIKA  BHAT  RIMA  ANANTKUMAR  PATEL  RUCHITA  ASHOKKUMAR  MACWAN  REKHABEN  KARABHAI  KARANGIYA  RAJNANDINI  DHANNALAL  PATIDAR  PATHARIYA  SARASWATI CHAND









     220    221  222   223   224  225   226   227   228   229  230  231  232  233  234   235   236   237     238   239]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                        31-08-2020                                                                             31-12-2020


     --     --    --          --   --    --   --   --    --   --   --    --    --    --    --     --    --  --



     19-01-2011  16-08-2016  04-08-2008  01-07-2016  17-08-2017  01-06-2013  12-08-2010  08-08-2013  01-01-2014  04-02-2010  01-07-2016  10-08-2017  01-02-2016  01-01-2014  02-07-2018  24-07-2018  07-12-2017  12-11-2018  14-05-2018  01-01-2019










     Yes    Yes   Yes   No    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes  No








     127    62    156   198   166  104   187  104  108   264  144  57    150   96    56    52     90    73  127  34







     Ph.D   M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  B.Sc.  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.Tech  MBA  M.Tech  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.E.  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)  MPT(Physio)







     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female


     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Lecturer  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     33     29    41    40    42   32    39   35   37    43   37   28    38    31    28    29     31    30  36  29





     SAGAR  RAMCHANDRA  CHOKSHI  SAGARKUMAR  JAGDISHBHAI  PATEL  SAMIR  GUNVANTBHAI  PATEL  SANDIP  BHIKHUBHAI  PATEL  SANJAYKUMAR HEMRAJ PANJABI  SANKETKUMAR  BHARATBHAI  SUTHAR  SANSKRUTI  VRIJLAL PATEL  SAPNA BHAVIN  PATEL  SATAYU CHANDRASHEKHA  R TRAVADI  SHILPA R  DALWADI  SIDDARAM  SHIVAJI SARATE  SNEHA  ASHVINKUMAR  PADHIAR  SNEHAL  JATINKUMAR  BHATT  SUJALKUMAR  VINODKUMAR  DADHANIYA  RUTVI  ARVINDBHAI  THAKOR  SHRADDHA  PARESHKUMAR  VYAS  SHWETA  DEVENDRABHAI  DA









     240    241   242   243   244  245   246  247  248   249  250  251   252   253   254   255    256   257  258  259]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular










     --   --    --     --  --  --    --    --    --     --    --   --    --   --    --    --    --    --     --



     21-01-2019  17-06-2019  12-06-2019  05-07-2019  28-03-2016  01-01-2014  01-07-2010  01-10-2015  14-04-2011  01-09-2010  06-07-2018  11-12-2013  01-01-2009  01-04-2016  16-01-2012  01-02-2016  06-07-2015  06-11-2000  20-05-2015










     Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes    Yes








     42   29    29     37  64  105   182   168   165    131   81   104   151  64    124   91    141   262    321







     BPT  B.Sc.  M.Tech  M.Sc.  MPT(Physio)  M.E.  Ph.D  MCA  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Sc.  Ph.D  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D






     Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male



                Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor


     Lecturer  Other                 Professor                Other                                   Professor  Professor










     25   25    26     26  29  32    38    39    37     33    30   36    34   29    36    32    35    45     48



     SONI ARCHI  DILIPBHAI  SHREYASKUMAR  HEMANTBHAI  PATEL  SHIVAM HARSHADKUMAR  RIBADIYA  SANTOSH OJHA  SWENI ATULKUMAR SHAH  TRUSHA  RONAKKUMAR  PATEL  TRUSHIT  KIRTIKUMAR  UPADHYAYA  TUSHAR  GUNVANTRAY  MEHTA  UMANG HARISHCHANDRA  SHAH  UPESH  PARBHUBHAI  PATEL  URVESHKUMAR SUNILKUMAR SONI  VAIBHAV  KIRITKUMAR  PATEL  VAISHALI HARDIK  KORIA  VANDITABEN  SANATKUMAR  SONI  VIBHABEN  NARENDRABHAI  PARMAR  VIDHI  VINODCHANDRA  THAKAR  VIJAY  MAHENDRABHAI  MAKWANA  VIJAYKU











     260  261   262    263  264  265  266  267   268    269   270  271   272  273   274   275   276   277    278]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting






            26-06-2021


     --         --  --    --   --   --    --    --    --    --   --    --   --   --    --   --    --    --  --  --  --



     01-01-2014  11-03-2013  27-07-2010  05-02-2014  23-06-2014  27-12-2012  23-07-2011  01-07-2006  16-08-2016  01-02-2017  01-08-2014  23-07-2011  01-09-2018  01-09-2018  26-07-2018  23-07-2018  15-10-2018  11-10-2018  01-09-2009  01-11-2017  05-11-2019  08-01-2020










     Yes    No  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes








     93     106  156  132  86  122  131   250   77    86    81   121   140  190  51    60   69    37    528  84  312  94







     M.E.   M.Tech  M.Sc.(Nursing)  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Sc.  MPT(Physio)  Master of Optometry  M.Tech  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  B.Sc.  MBBS  M.D  Ph.D  M.D







     Male   Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male


     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Other  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other














     30     33  38  36    32   32   33    45    33    31    31   36    34   36   27    39   36    25    64  34  57  31


       HASMUKHBHAI  RAVINDRAN NAIR  VIPIN  VAGERIYA  HARSHADBHAI  VIRAL DHIRAJLAL  PARBATBHAI TANK  RAJENDRABHAI  NANDURBARKAR  THAKORBHAI  YOGESH SURESH  CHANDRAKANT  SWAYAMPRAKASH  KANTILAL PATEL  TAPAN AMRUTLAL  TUSHARKUMAR  YOGESHWARI FAKIRBHAI PATEL  VANARAJSINH  JASHAVANTSINH  DHIRUBHAI  BHAVIK SHELAT  UTSAV PAREKH  Dr Hemant Tiwari  Paresh Ashokbhai


     VIKAS  PANCHAL  VINEETHA  VIPUL  VYAS  PANARA  VISHAL  VISHAL  MEHTA  VYOMESH  PRAHLAD  YASHREE  PATEL  YOGESH  RAVJIBHAI  VAGHELA  TIWARI  ZANKHAN  SONARA  PATEL  VIDHIBEN  PANDYA  SOLANKI  VASVIBEN  PARMAR  Varsat








     279    280  281  282  283  284  285  286   287   288   289  290   291  292  293   294  295   296   297  298  299  300]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                 31-10-2020                                                                      31-12-2020


     --   --  --    --  --   --    --  --  --    --   --   --    --    --   --   --   --  --           --    --



     23-06-2020  10-03-2012  01-11-2000  04-11-2015  01-09-2009  05-03-2001  23-06-2016  16-05-2018  01-09-2018  01-09-2018  21-07-2012  07-07-2017  09-07-2012  10-07-2006  02-01-2017  01-04-2016  01-09-2017  01-07-2010  23-06-2014  01-01-2019  13-07-2006  01-04-2016










     Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  No  Yes   Yes








     46   454  303  537  296  684  147  80  160  218  109  105  109  181  188  145  74  140  97  94    181   84






     M. Phil  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  MBA  MCA  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  MCA  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  MPT(Physio)  Ph.D  MCA







     Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female



     Assistant Professor  Professor  Professor  Professor  Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     32   70  51  70  46  90  35   31  38  41    33   32   32    38    39   35   42   36  30     32    36    29




     Mukshita Y  Dharangadhra  BHARAT G PATEL  DEVANG JOSHI  HARESH JANI  KALAPI PATEL  DR SHIVPRASAD  KOSTA  DIVYANG  VAIJNATH  PUROHIT  NEEL PATEL  MITTAL NIRBHIK  DESAI  NILAYKUMAR  MOHITKUMAR  VAIDYA  MOCHI PRATIK  KANTILAL  MOHAMMAD  HUSAIN BOHARA  MRUDANG  DAXESHKUMAR  PANDYA  MRUGENDRASINH  LAXMANSINH  RAHEVAR  MRUNALI  RASHMIN PATEL  MUBINA SHAQIL  MALIK  MURALI MOHAN  SHARAFF  NEHA HIRENSINH  RAJPUT  NEHAL  SANDIPKUMAR  PATEL  NENCY  KALPESHBHAI  PANDYA  NIKITA










     301  302  303  304  305  306  307  308  309  310  311  312  313  314  315  316  317  318  319  320  321  322]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular










     --     --    --    --   --    --   --  --   --     --     --  --    --    --    --   --    --  --    --    --



     27-12-2007  18-07-2011  02-07-2007  09-06-2015  18-01-2016  01-06-2018  22-10-2018  26-12-2018  02-03-2020  13-08-2019  27-01-2021  01-04-2016  01-07-2008  07-07-2008  05-07-2018  23-07-2013  10-09-2015  02-01-2017  21-12-2015  01-05-2004










     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes








     164    122   320   82   71    42   416  66  17     24     44  75    157   169   79   182   180  143  284   207







     Ph.D   MCA   Ph.D  M.Tech  M.E.  MPT(Physio)  M.Sc.  M. Pharm  Ph.D  M.Sc.  MD  MCA  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech  MSc(Mathematics)  MPT(Physio)  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D







     Male   Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male


     Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Dean / Principal /  Director / Vice  Chancellor  Professor














     37     34    48    31   29    27   64  28   31     24     29  30    36    38    30   41    41  33    49    41


       DHIRENKUMAR  PRAVINCHANDRA  NILAYKUMAR  ARVINDBHAI  NILESH KUMAR  DILIPKUMAR  MITVA MAUNIL  MUNEER FARZANA  KAMLESHBHAI  OMPRAKASH  MOHAMMAD  AKHLAQUE MOHAMMAD SAMI  Mona Megha  POOJABEN  VARUNKUMAR  YASHVANTRAI  HASMUKHRAI  AMRUTLAL PATEL  CHETANBHAI  P RATAN KHUMAN  PADMAVATHI  JAGDISHPRASAD  PALASH  MANDAL  DILIPKUMAR SHAH


     NILAY  SOLANKI  NILAY  GANATRA  PATEL  DUBEY  NIPUN  GOSAI  THAKKAR  NIKUNJ  PAREKH  NILESH  PANDEY  AHMAD  PAREKH  NIRAJ  VYAS  NIRAV  BHATT  NIRPEX  NIRUBEN  PATEL  BINDULAL  PARTH








     323    324   325   326  327   328  329  330  331   332    333  334  335   336   337  338   339  340  341   342]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                30-06-2021                                                                 27-10-2020      10-09-2020


     --     --         --    --   --  --   --    --     --    --    --   --    --    --         --   --         --



     01-02-2016  01-09-2012  05-07-2018  01-06-2012  27-08-2012  05-07-2011  01-11-2000  01-01-2007  19-07-2010  25-02-2011  23-06-2014  17-05-2013  17-07-2014  25-10-2017  12-11-2018  14-07-2017  15-05-2018  10-01-2019  27-12-2018  28-09-2017










     Yes    Yes  No    Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes   No   Yes  Yes   No   Yes








     78     137  40    110   174  170  398  181  142    142   97    147  85    132   146   75   121  131   35   50






     M.Tech  M.E.  M.Tech  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  M. Pharm  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  MPT(Physio)  B.Sc.








     Male   Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female


     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other














     30     44  29     33    37   40  61   39    36     33    30    37   30    31    39    30   36   34    25   25


       SANDIPKUMAR  PANKAJBHAI  PINAL CHIRAG  MAHAVIRPRASAD  JAYANTIBHAI  SUKUMARAN  VAIDHIYALINGAM  JOHNBHAI DABHI  DHIMANTKUMAR  JYOTISHBHAI  BHANUBHAI  PRITESHKUMAR  NATAVARLAL  PRAJAPATI  PRANAV PATEL  GIRJASHANKAR  NAVINCHANDRA  PAYALBEN PURSHOTTAMBHA  I CHAUHAN  PHENILKUMAR  PRAKASH BUCH  PRATHYAKSH  JANARDHANAN  PRAGNESHKUMAR  ROHITBHAI  PANKTI ASHOK  DHRUPALKUMAR


     PATEL   PATEL  PINKIBEN  SHARMA  POONAM  THANKI  PRABHIN  PRAKASH  PRAKASH  PRANAV  DESAI  PRANAV  VYAS  PRATIK  PANCHAL  PRIYANKA  RAJAT  PANDEY  PARTH  GOEL  MAKWANA  PATEL  PRIYANCY  PATEL








     343    344  345   346   347  348  349  350  351    352   353   354  355   356   357   358  359  360   361  362]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






                                      31-03-2021                                               23-07-2020


     --     --    --   --    --   --       --    --     --  --     --  --  --    --  --    --         --    --   --



     24-06-2019  22-07-2019  01-08-2017  12-10-2015  01-04-2016  22-06-2009  13-10-2008  01-01-2003  01-07-2014  27-12-2011  15-11-2010  01-12-2018  16-08-2018  18-01-2016  02-06-2011  16-01-2017  01-08-2018  12-11-2018  01-08-2018  25-07-2018  02-07-2018










     Yes    Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  No  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  No   Yes   Yes  Yes








     39     62    64   117   158  158  154  223  133    116  192   103  142  73  222  123  49  31     123   72   61






     M.Tech  M.Tech  MPT(Physio)  M.Sc.(Nursing)  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Tech  M. Pharm  Ph.D  Ph.D  MCA  M.E.  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  B.Sc.  Ph.D  M.E.  M.Tech







     Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female



     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     27     28    29   33    40   36  34   42    32     33  41     33  39  29    47  33    32  24     34    29   28




     PRIYALBA BHUPENDRASINH  VAGHELA  NISHAT  ANVARHUSEN  SHAIKH  HETA RAJNIKANT  PATEL  HETAL  JITENDRABHAI  SHAH  HETALBEN PUNJABHAI PATEL  HIMANSHU A  PATEL  HITESH NATVARLAL PATEL  HITESHRI  KAMLESHBHAI  SHASTRI  JAGRAT  PUSHAKARBHAI  MEHTA  JAGRUTI BRIJESH  PRAJAPATI  JAIMIN  NAVINCHANDRA  UNDAVIA  JAGRUTI  LALJIBHAI DESAI  KRISHNA  KANT  JIGNESHKUMAR  SUBHASBHAI  PATEL  KINNARI PAREKH  KIRANKUMAR  GORDHANBHAI  PATEL  JANKIBEN  KIRITBHAI PATEL  JINALKUMARI GHANSHYAMB










     363    364   365  366   367  368  369  370  371    372  373   374  375  376  377  378  379  380  381   382  383]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting






              31-07-2020                                                                            12-11-2020  12-09-2020  30-09-2020


     --   --      --     --  --     --  --     --  --   --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --      --



     11-08-2018  16-08-2018  25-06-2018  11-06-2019  23-07-2012  23-08-2019  13-08-2019  01-04-2021  19-03-2021  06-10-2008  01-11-2000  01-11-2000  01-07-2016  01-06-2011  04-04-2011  03-06-2013  01-11-2006  11-04-2011  01-06-2020  16-03-2020  17-10-2016  15-05-2012  02-03-2020  25-07-2020  25-07-2020  04-09-2020  01-01-2019










     Yes  Yes  No  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  No  No  No  Yes








     137  63  26  93     138  117   34  44     3   152  247  259  60  120  122  95  217  158  20  78  56  109  87  72  396  180  30







     Ph.D  M.Sc.  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.E.  M.Sc.  M.E.  Ph.D  MBA  M.Sc.  M.E.  MCA  MBA  MCA  MBA  Ph.D  MBA  MBA  MBA  MCA  MCA  MBA  Ph.D  B.Sc.  Ph.D  M. Pharm







     Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female


     Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor














     34   28  27  33     34  36     26  29     56  37   45  44  36  32  33  31  47  48  32  28  30  34  30  33  69  42  28


     MANDAR DILIP  KULKARNI  MANNA  DEBNATH  MICHELE JAYKANT  MISTRY  MIKINBHAI  RAKESHBHAI  PATEL  MINAL NIRAV  SHAH  MADHAV  MUKUNDBHAI  AJWALIA  KARAN SITARAM  MORJE  URVI  YOGESHKUMAR  BHATT  YOGESHWAR  PRASAD KOSTA  SHAHNAWAJ A  PATHAN  JIGNESH PATEL  JAYMIN DESAI  DIPEN PATEL  DIPAL SHETH  KRUNAL PATEL  AANAL PATEL  DILIP GOSAI  MUKESH YADAV  KRUTEN PATEL  PARTH PATEL  NAITIK PATEL  NIRMAL PATEL  MAULESH PATEL  HARDIK SHAH  JUSABBHAI U  MEMON  ASHA VERMA  BINDUKUMAR












     384  385  386  387  388  389   390  391   392  393  394  395  396  397  398  399  400  401  402  403  404  405  406  407  408  409  410]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular






     12-12-2020  27-02-2021  15-06-2021  18-05-2021  --  15-12-2020  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --







     07-07-2020  13-10-2020  15-03-2021  19-11-2020  01-01-2016  22-10-2020  03-08-2017  17-06-2019  31-10-2020  02-03-2021  22-03-2021  17-05-2021  01-11-2020  01-04-2021  01-03-2021  21-04-2021  01-02-2021  30-11-2020  10-04-2021  08-03-2021  25-01-2021  18-03-2021











     No   No  No  No  Yes  No  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes   Yes   Yes







     46   216  58  156  552  84  77  24  22   180  21    54    465  63    18    55  75  293  44    169    10    3







     M.D  M.D  M.Sc.  MD  M.E.  MBA  M.S  B.Sc.  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  MBA  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Tech  Ph.D  Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  Ph.D






     Female  Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Male



                                        Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor



     Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Professor  Other  Other                     Other









     31   44  31  47  72  34  34  27    24    44   26    38    66   27    24    45  35  54   33    40     24    30



     JINCY JEBIN  JACOB  SANJAY GUPTA  DHARA PATEL  DEVA JAPA  VIJAY SAFAYA  CS DIVYESH  PATEL  AMITA VIRAN  PATEL  ARCHANABEN  RAHULKUMAR  PATEL  BANSARI  BHAVDIPBHAI  PATEL  BHAVESHKUMAR JIVABHAI PARMAR  BRIJESHKUMAR  YOGESHBHAI  PANCHAL  CHIRAG  ISHWARBHAI  PATEL  DATTA BABURAO  MADAMWAR  DHARTIBEN  NEELKUMAR  PATEL  DHRUVI DHARMENDRAVAN  GOSAI  GEETA MARMAT  HEMA RAJNIKANT  PATEL  HOMA ASHWIN  PATEL  JIGNESH  RAMESHBHAI  PATEL  MINAL  PARIMALBHAI  PATEL  MOHITSINH DHA











     411  412  413  414  415  416  417  418  419  420  421  422  423  424  425  426  427  428  429  430   431   432]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Regular  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Visiting










     --   --    --   --    --     --  --  --  --  --   --   --    --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --  --



     01-10-2020  18-08-2005  17-05-2021  01-12-2020  21-12-2020  01-05-2021  09-10-2019  25-01-2021  17-06-2021  08-04-2021  17-11-2017  17-11-2017  07-05-2020  22-07-2020  22-07-2020  08-06-2020  22-07-2020  08-06-2020  01-01-2021  10-06-2020  06-07-2020  10-06-2020  01-01-2021  01-01-2021










     Yes  Yes   Yes  Yes   Yes    Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes  Yes








     164  190   30   58    190    195  255  36  18  28  40  36    15  24  12  20  11  30  7   12  11  12  7   7







     Ph.D  Ph.D  M.E.  M.E.  Ph.D  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  Ph.D  M.Sc.  M.E.  M.Tech  M.Tech  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Tech  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.







     Male  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Male  Male  Male  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female  Female  Female  Female  Male  Female  Female


     Assistant Professor  Associate Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Other  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other  Other














     36   40    26   26    39     48  44  35  25  29   28   33    26  32  26  31  24  32  30  27  24  25  23  25

     MUKESHKUMAR  RAMSEVAK PAL  NIRALI  BHAVINKUMAR  DABHI  PARTH RANJIT  SINGH  SACHIN  HITESHBHAI  PATEL  SOHIL  DINESHKUMAR  PANDYA  SUCHITRA BARGE  Nilam Patel  Hemant Gupta  Kesha Ronakbhai  Patel  Naiswita  Dineshchandra  Parmar  Vivek Shamjibhai  Ayar  Vivekkumar  Vinubhai  Brahmbhatt  Parth Bambhaniya  Kirti Parwani  Komal Parmar  Rupesh Kumar Tipu  MODI KRISHNA  HIRENKUMAR  Dixa Sharma  NIDHIBEN  SUDHAKARBHAI  SONI  Leyon Selvin Raj A  Dimpy Patel  Viradiya Ravi













     433  434   435  436   437    438  439  440  441  442  443  444  445  446  447  448  449  450  451  452  453  454  455  456]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[Visiting  Visiting  Visiting  Regular  Regular










     --     --    --    --   --



     01-01-2021  01-01-2021  01-01-2021  13-06-2016  13-06-2016










     Yes    Yes   Yes   Yes  Yes








                        53   72
     7      7     7





     M.Sc.  M.Sc.  M.Sc.  MSc(IT)  MSc(IT)







     Female  Male  Male  Male  Male



                        Assistant Professor  Assistant Professor



     Other  Other  Other









     23     27    27    32   31





     MAINAVI  MUKESHKUMAR  PATEL  AKASHKUMAR  MANUBHAI  PUROHIT  PATEL  DIVYESHKUMAR  KANUBHAI  SUNNY VIJAYBHAI  PATEL  ERNEST JOHN  STEVENS









     457    458   459   460  461]]></page></pages></Search>